<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<code-table xml:id="date-encoding-code">
    <code-table-name>date-encoding-code</code-table-name>
    <status>finished</status>
    <form>closed</form>
    <basis>http://www.loc.gov/standards/mods/v3/mods-userguide-generalapp.html</basis>
    <description/>
    <notes/>
    <tab-id>origin</tab-id>
    <tab-id>part</tab-id>
    <tab-id>record-info</tab-id>
    <tab-id>related</tab-id>
    <tab-id>related-abbreviated</tab-id>
    <tab-id>related-xlink</tab-id>
    <tab-id>subject</tab-id>
    <items>
        <item>
            <value/>
            <label>(none selected)</label>
        </item>
        <item>
            <label>YYYY-MM-DD</label>
            <value>w3cdtf</value>
            <description>This value identifies dates following the W3C profile of ISO 8601, Date and
                Time Formats, that specifies the extended format for dates using the pattern:
                YYYY-MM-DD. If hours, minutes, and seconds are also needed the following pattern is
                used: YYYY-MM-DDThh:mm:ss.</description>
        </item>
        <item>
            <label>ISO 8601</label>
            <value>iso8601</value>
            <description>This value identifies formatted dates allowed in ISO 8601 which use the
                alternative described as "basic" (i.e., with minimum number of separators) rather
                than "extended" (i.e., with separators). This alternative specified in the standard
                uses the following date patterns: YYYY; YYYY-MM if only year and month given;
                YYYYMMDD if year, month, and day are included (hours, minutes, seconds may also be
                added: Thhmmss.s). It is also used for other encodings specified in ISO 8601, e.g.,
                date ranges, which are in the form of
                &lt;date/time&gt;/&lt;date/time&gt;.</description>
        </item>
        <item>
            <label>MARC</label>
            <value>marc</value>
            <description>This value identifies formatted according to MARC 21 rules in field
                008/07-14 for dates of publication/issuance. Thus, this would only apply to the
                attribute in &lt;dateIssued&gt;. Examples include: YYYY (for year), MMDD (for month
                and day), 19uu (MARC convention showing unknown digits in a year date), 9999 (MARC
                convention showing that the end year date has not occurred or is not
                known).</description>
        </item>
        <item>
            <label>Extended Date/Time Format</label>
            <value>edtf</value>
            <description>This value is used for dates coded according to Extended Date/Time Format
                which is consistent with ISO 8601 but extends it to express special forms of dates
                that are not covered by w3cdtf and iso8601, such as open ended ranges.</description>
        </item>
        <item>
            <label>TEMPER</label>
            <value>temper</value>
            <description>This value is used for dates coded according to Temporal Enumerated Ranges.
                TEMPER is a simple date and time syntax for representing points, lists, and ranges
                of timestamps. The syntax is designed to be easy to parse and for humans to read,
                and compatible with basic lexical sorting algorithms.</description>
        </item>
        <item type="added">
            <label>text</label>
            <value>text</value>
            <description>This value is used only for dates coded according to MARC 21 rules in field
                008/07-14 for dates of publication/issuance. Thus, this would only apply to the
                attribute in dateIssued. Examples include: 19uu (a MARC convention to show unknown
                digits in a date), 9999 (a MARC convention showing that the end date has not
                occurred or is not known).</description>
        </item>
    </items>
</code-table>