<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<!--let $code-table :=
-->
<code-table xml:id="hint-code">
    <code-table-name>hint-code</code-table-name>
    <items>
        <item xml:id="hint-code_save">
            <help>
                <p>Every time you click a tab (including the current one), your input is saved. </p>
                <p>When you click "Finish Editing", your input is saved, and you return to the
                    search interface where your record is displayed. </p>
                <p>The record is saved inside the folder you marked before opening the editor or the
                    folder from which you opened it for re-editing.</p>
                <p>Be aware that you are only logged in for 30 minutes and that when your session
                    times out, you will be returned to the search interface and what you have input
                    without saving cannot be retrieved.</p>
                <p>You can always see when your record was last saved, in the line above.</p>
                <p>Note that if you reload the web page, your last edits are lost.</p>
                <p>You can keep your session alive for another 30 minutes by clicking any tab. When
                    your session is about to expire, you are prompted to keep it alive and given 5
                    minutes to react.</p>
                <p>If you know that you may not be able to finish a record, it is best to click
                    "Finish Editing" and return later to continue editing it.</p>
                <p>You can continue editing the record by finding it and clicking the "Edit Record"
                    button inside the record's detail view.</p>
                <p>If you wish to discard your edits, click "Cancel Editing" at the bottom of the
                    page. None of the edits you have made will then be saved and you will be shown
                    the original record again.</p>
            </help>
            <tab-id>edit.xq</tab-id>
        </item>
        <item xml:id="hint-code_relatedItem">
            <help>
                <p> Information that identifies other resources related to the one being described.
                </p>
            </help>
            <local-name>type</local-name>
            <tab-id>related</tab-id>
            <tab-id>related-abbreviated</tab-id>
            <tab-id>related-xlink</tab-id>
        </item>
        <item xml:id="hint-code_relatedItem-type">
            <help>
                <p> The type field describes the relationship between the resource in Related Item
                    and the resource in the parent record.</p>
                <p> Use one of the following values: Host, Constituent, Series, Other Version.</p>
                <p> "Host" is used to describe a host or parent resource, for example a book or
                    periodical in which an article appears or a collection in which an item belongs. </p>
                <p> "Constituent" is used to describe parts of the resource, except information that
                    falls within the scope of the Table Of Contents element. </p>
                <p> "Series" is used to describe a named series of which the resource is a part. </p>
                <p> "Other Version" is used to describe other versions of the work contained in the
                    resource. </p>
            </help>
            <local-name>type</local-name>
            <tab-id>related</tab-id>
            <tab-id>related-abbreviated</tab-id>
            <tab-id>related-xlink</tab-id>
        </item>
        <item xml:id="hint-code_relatedItem-xlink_href">
            <help>
                <p> The type field describes the relationship between the resource in Related Item
                    and the resource in the parent record.</p>
                <p> Use one of the following values: Host, Constituent, Series, Other Version.</p>
                <p> "Host" is used to describe a host or parent resource, for example a book or
                    periodical in which an article appears or a collection in which an item belongs. </p>
                <p> "Constituent" is used to describe parts of the resource, except information that
                    falls within the scope of the Table Of Contents element. </p>
                <p> "Series" is used to describe a named series of which the resource is a part. </p>
                <p> "Other Version" is used to describe other versions of the work contained in the
                    resource. </p>
            </help>
            <local-name>type</local-name>
            <tab-id>related</tab-id>
            <tab-id>related-abbreviated</tab-id>
            <tab-id>related-xlink</tab-id>
        </item>
        <item xml:id="hint-code_recordIdentifier">
            <help>
                <p>Used to record the system control number assigned by the organization creating,
                    using, or distributing the record.</p>
            </help>
            <local-name>descriptionStandard</local-name>
            <tab-id>record-info</tab-id>
        </item>
        <item xml:id="hint-code_record-content-source">
            <help>
                <p>Contains the code or name of the organization whose system control number is
                    located in the Record Identifier element.</p>
                <p>The Library of Congress maintains <a href="http://www.loc.gov/standards/sourcelist/organization.html">http://www.loc.gov/standards/sourcelist/organization.html</a> (Organization
                    Code Source Codes), an online listing of source values.</p>
            </help>
            <local-name>descriptionStandard</local-name>
            <tab-id>record-info</tab-id>
        </item>
        <item xml:id="hint-code_descriptionStandard">
            <help>
                <p>Here are noted any specific rules used for the description.</p>
            </help>
            <local-name>descriptionStandard</local-name>
            <tab-id>record-info</tab-id>
        </item>
        <item xml:id="hint-code_languageOfCataloging">
            <help>
                <p> Note here the language used in cataloging the current record. Use both Text and
                    Code input. </p>
            </help>
            <local-name>languageOfCataloging</local-name>
            <tab-id>record-info</tab-id>
        </item>
        <item xml:id="hint-code_recordContentSource">
            <help>
                <p> The code or name of the organization that either created or modified the
                    original record. This information can be useful to trace the provenance of a
                    particular metadata record. The name or code should be pulled from an
                    authoritative list and indicated in Authority. Record Content Source should be
                    repeated for each code or name recorded. </p>
            </help>
            <local-name>recordContentSource</local-name>
            <tab-id>record-info</tab-id>
        </item>
        <item xml:id="hint-code_recordOrigin">
            <help>
                <p> Record Origin is intended to show the origin, or provenance of the record. Note
                    the original format and transformation process if the record has been
                    transformed from a record in another format. </p>
            </help>
            <local-name>recordOrigin</local-name>
            <tab-id>record-info</tab-id>
        </item>
        <item xml:id="hint-code_recordIdentifier">
            <help>
                <p> Record Identifier is used to record the system control number assigned by the
                    organization creating, using, or distributing the record. Consult <a href="http://www.loc.gov/marc/organizations/org-search.php">http://www.loc.gov/marc/organizations/org-search.php</a> (MARC Code List
                    for Organizations) and <a href="http://www.oclc.org/contacts/libraries/">OCLC
                        Participating Institutions</a>
                </p>
            </help>
            <local-name>recordIdentifier</local-name>
            <tab-id>record-info</tab-id>
        </item>
        <item xml:id="hint-code_recordChangeDate">
            <help>
                <p>The date(s) on which the record has been changed.</p>
            </help>
            <local-name>recordChangeDate</local-name>
            <tab-id>record-info</tab-id>
        </item>
        <item xml:id="hint-code_recordCreationDate">
            <help>
                <p>The date on which the record was first created.</p>
            </help>
            <local-name>recordCreationDate</local-name>
            <tab-id>record-info</tab-id>
        </item>
        <item xml:id="hint-code_recordInfo">
            <help>
                <p>Information about the metadata record.</p>
                <p>This type of administrative information can help establish the provenance of a
                    metadata record and may enable better interpretation of the content of the
                    record. Record Information may also include information that is relevant only to
                    the creating or managing institution. This type of administrative information
                    can help establish the provenance of a metadata record and may enable better
                    interpretation of the content of the record. </p>
            </help>
            <local-name>recordInfo</local-name>
            <tab-id>record-info</tab-id>
        </item>
        <item xml:id="hint-code_table-of-contents">
            <help>
                <p> A description of the contents of a resource.</p>
                <p> A Table Of Contents can be rendered e.g. with dashes separating the chapter
                    titles.</p>
                <p> Use of Table Of Contents should be determined by the complexity of the digital
                    object and whether or not the information is readily available. If more
                    structured information is needed, consider using Related Item with the
                    type="constituent" field instead. Table Of Contents can also be used as an empty
                    field with an XLink field to link to an external table of contents. </p>
            </help>
            <local-name>tableOfContents</local-name>
            <tab-id>table-of-contents</tab-id>
            <tab-id>compact-c</tab-id>
            <tab-id>compact-d</tab-id>
        </item>
        <item xml:id="hint-code_abstract">
            <help>
                <p> Abstract is used to record a succinct summary of some aspect of the content of
                    the resource. </p>
                <p> Use one Abstract in every record, except when Title Information serves as an
                    adequate summary of the content of the resource. </p>
                <p> When creating a record for a digital surrogate, record a summary of the content
                    of the original resource. If only a portion of the resource was digitized,
                    summarize only that portion. </p>
                <p> A link may be supplied in lieu of or in addition to a summary of the content. </p>
                <p> Repeat Abstract as many times as necessary. </p>
            </help>
            <local-name>abstract</local-name>
            <tab-id>abstract</tab-id>
            <tab-id>compact-c</tab-id>
            <tab-id>compact-d</tab-id>
        </item>
        <item xml:id="hint-code_shareable">
            <help>
                <p>Identifies data that cannot be shared outside the institution.</p>
                <p>This attribute is used with shareable="no" for data that may be proprietary or is
                    rights protected and should not be used outside of a local system (such as
                    providing to harvesters).</p>
            </help>
            <hint/>
            <local-name>shareable</local-name>
            <tab-id>table-of-contents</tab-id>
            <tab-id>abstract</tab-id>
        </item>
        <item xml:id="hint-code_abstract-type">
            <help>
                <p>Identifies what type of summary is recorded.</p>
                <p>There is no controlled list of abstract types. Examples include scope, subject,
                    content advice, review.</p>
            </help>
            <local-name>type</local-name>
            <tab-id>abstract</tab-id>
        </item>
        <item xml:id="hint-code_toc-type">
            <help>
                <p>Identifies what type of contents is recorded.</p>
                <p>There is no controlled list of table of contents types.</p>
            </help>
            <local-name>type</local-name>
            <tab-id>table-of-contents</tab-id>
        </item>
        <item xml:id="hint-code_accessCondition">
            <help>
                <p>Information about restrictions imposed on access to a resource is noted here.</p>
                <p>Use Access Condition to indicate rights relating to access and use of digital
                    resources. State clearly any restrictions on use of the digital resource,
                    including explicitly mentioning lack of copyright restrictions when the digital
                    resource is in the public domain. Also provide contact information for use by
                    end users who wish to require permissions for publication, exhibit, or other
                    types of dissemination.</p>
                <p>An XLink may be supplied in lieu of or in addition to the content noted in Access
                    Condition. If, for example, you maintain rights information relating to specific
                    resources on a website, you may provide a URL for that website in lieu of a
                    textual rights statement. When doing so, you should provide enough textual
                    explanation in Access Condition, along with the URL, to make the purpose of the
                    URL clear to end users.</p>
                <p> Whenever possible, consider using a standard license such as Creative Commons
                    and/or a rights expression language such as the Open Digital Rights Language
                    (ODRL) specification.</p>
            </help>
            <local-name>accessCondition</local-name>
            <tab-id>access-condition</tab-id>
        </item>
        <item xml:id="hint-code_url-access">
            <help>
                <p>Indicates the type of resource that the user will access when following the URL
                    link.</p>
                <p>This attribute is particularly useful to provide a flag in the context of OAI
                    service providers harvesting metadata.</p>
                <p>The following values may be used with the access attribute:</p>
                <ul>
                    <li>preview – Indicates a link to a thumbnail or snippet of text.</li>
                    <li>raw object – Indicates a direct link to the object described (e.g., a jpg or
                        pdf document). Used only when the object is represented by a single
                        file.</li>
                    <li>object in context – Indicates a link to the object within the context of its
                        environment (with associated metadata, navigation, etc.)</li>
                </ul>
            </help>
            <local-name>access</local-name>
            <tab-id>location</tab-id>
        </item>
        <item xml:id="hint-code_location-url-note">
            <help>
                <p>Includes notes that are associated with the link that is included as the value of
                    the URL element.</p>
                <p>Use the note attribute only when other attributes (access, usage, or
                    displayLabel) are not appropriate.</p>
            </help>
            <local-name>access</local-name>
            <tab-id>location</tab-id>
        </item>
        <item xml:id="hint-code_note-type">
            <help>
                <p>Describes the type of note that is recorded.</p>
            </help>
            <local-name>type</local-name>
            <tab-id>location</tab-id>
        </item>
        <item xml:id="hint-code_sublocation">
            <help>
                <p>Department, division, or section of an institution holding a copy of the
                    resource.</p>
                <p>Sublocation may be repeated for multiple equivalent items in different
                    sublocations within the institution named in Physical Location.</p>
            </help>
            <local-name>sublocation</local-name>
            <tab-id>location</tab-id>
        </item>
        <item xml:id="hint-code_holdingSimple">
            <help>
                <p>General information about what the institution identified in Physical Location
                    holds of the resource and its specific location.</p>
                <p>Holdings information consists of copy-specific information about the resource,
                    information about the specific location within an institution, version
                    information, and other information that is peculiar to the institution.</p>
                <p>Holding Simple is a set of MODS internally defined elements and corresponds
                    roughly to summary holdings information. </p>
                <p>Holding Simple is a container element for the single subelement, Copy Information
                    which has several subelements.</p>
                <p>Holding Simple is not repeatable; if additional holdings statements are needed
                    for the resource, repeat Location with appropriate subelements</p>
                <p>For more information see <a href="http://www.loc.gov/standards/mods/v3/mods-holdings.html">http://www.loc.gov/standards/mods/v3/mods-holdings.html</a> (MODS Holdings
                    Information).</p>
            </help>
            <local-name>holdingSimple</local-name>
            <tab-id>location</tab-id>
        </item>
        <item xml:id="hint-code_location-form">
            <help>
                <p>Designation of a particular physical presentation of a resource.</p>
                <p>The Form subelement is equivalent to MODS Form under Physical Description.</p>
                <p>It may be included under Copy Information when the MODS record refers to multiple
                    forms and there is different detailed holdings information associated with each
                    form.</p>
                <p>Form is not repeatable; Copy Information is repeated within Holding Simple for
                    multiple forms.</p>
            </help>
            <local-name>form</local-name>
            <tab-id>location</tab-id>
        </item>
        <item xml:id="hint-code_location-form-type">
            <help>
                <p>May be used to specify whether the form concerns materials or techniques, for
                    example:</p>
                <ul>
                    <li>&lt;form type="material&gt;oil paint&lt;/form&gt;</li>
                    <li>&lt;form type="technique&gt;painting&lt;/form&gt;</li>
                </ul>
                <p>There are no controlled values for the type attribute.</p>
            </help>
            <local-name>type</local-name>
            <tab-id>location</tab-id>
        </item>
        <item xml:id="hint-code_location-note">
            <help>
                <p>Note relating to a specific copy of a document.</p>
                <p>Use for notes relating to the specific copy information of a resource that do not
                    fit in one of the other available subelements.</p>
                <p>A link may be supplied in lieu of or in addition to the content.</p>
                <p>Each note should be entered in a separate Note subelement.</p>
            </help>
            <local-name>note</local-name>
            <tab-id>location</tab-id>
        </item>
        <item xml:id="hint-code_location-url">
            <help>
                <p>URL is for an electronic location from which the resource is available. It is
                    recommended that all URLs used with the Location element be persistent. </p>
                <p>Note that Identifier is used for persistent identifiers that may or may not be
                    resolvable.</p>
                <p> The Location element with the URL subelement may be used to indicate locations
                    of additional versions of the digital resource such as thumbnails of the digital
                    resource. It is recommended that in these cases the access attribute be used to
                    help an aggregator determine what versions of the resource are available. Best
                    practice is that the "primary display" URL is a link to the resource with its
                    contextual material (for example metadata, navigation to the collection
                    homepage). If the primary link to a resource is to a stand-alone version of the
                    resource (such as a JPEG image only), an end user will have no context except
                    for the metadata on the service provider's site. At a minimum, the URL should
                    point to a page that contains the resource and a navigation bar that allows
                    users to reach the collection homepage. It is highly desirable that this page
                    also include the descriptive metadata for the resource.</p>
                <p>Use of the access attribute is recommended with all instances of URL. </p>
            </help>
            <local-name>url</local-name>
            <tab-id>location</tab-id>
        </item>
        <item xml:id="hint-code_location-usage">
            <help>
                <p>Indicates how the object represented by the link will be used.</p>
                <p>This attribute may be used to indicate special purpose of the URL in the element,
                    which may be marked as such using the access attribute.</p>
                <p>The following values is defined:</p>
                <ul>
                    <li>primary display – Indicates that the link is the most appropriate to display
                        for end users.</li>
                    <li>primary – Added for consistency when usage was defined for several other
                        elements. This value has the same definition as "primary display". The
                        intent is that "primary display" will be depricated in favor of "primary" in
                        a future MODS version. Use of " primary" instead of "primary display" is
                        therefore recommended in this attribute.</li>
                </ul>
            </help>
            <local-name>usage</local-name>
            <tab-id>location</tab-id>
        </item>
        <item xml:id="hint-code_electronicLocator">
            <help>
                <p>The Uniform Resource Location of the resource.</p>
            </help>
            <local-name>electronicLocator</local-name>
            <tab-id>location</tab-id>
        </item>
        <item xml:id="hint-code_copyInformation">
            <help>
                <p>Information about a specific tangible instance of a bibliographic resource or set
                    which comprises one or more pieces via indication of sublocation and/or
                    locator.</p>
                <p>Copy Information is a container element. Data is entered in the subelements.</p>
            </help>
            <local-name>copyInformation</local-name>
            <tab-id>location</tab-id>
        </item>
        <item xml:id="hint-code_dateLastAccessed">
            <help>
                <p>Intended to express the date that a digital resource has been accessed remotely. </p>
                <p>This attribute may be useful to a user because of the volatility of Web content.
                    There is no encoding scheme specified for use with this attribute, however, a
                    structured date is recommended.</p>
            </help>
            <local-name>dateLastAccessed</local-name>
            <tab-id>location</tab-id>
        </item>
        <item xml:id="hint-code_affiliation">
            <help>
                <p>Affiliation contains the name, address, etc. of an organisation with which the
                    person in Name was associated when the resource was created.</p>
                <p>If the information is readily available, it may be included.</p>
            </help>
            <local-name>affiliation</local-name>
            <tab-id>name</tab-id>
            <tab-id>mads</tab-id>
        </item>
        <item xml:id="hint-code_altRepGroup">
            <help>
                <p> Alternate Representation Groups is used to link alternate representations of the
                    same element content, such as different scripts, transliterations, and
                    translations. The same attribute value is applied to each of the element
                    instances to be linked.</p>
            </help>
            <local-name>altRepGroup</local-name>
            <tab-id>name</tab-id>
            <tab-id>part</tab-id>
            <tab-id>related</tab-id>
            <tab-id>related-abbreviated</tab-id>
            <tab-id>related-xlink</tab-id>
            <tab-id>physical-description</tab-id>
            <tab-id>target-audience</tab-id>
            <tab-id>language</tab-id>
            <tab-id>subject</tab-id>
            <tab-id>classification</tab-id>
            <tab-id>note</tab-id>
            <tab-id>access-condition</tab-id>
            <tab-id>table-of-contents</tab-id>
            <tab-id>identifier</tab-id>
            <tab-id>location</tab-id>
            <tab-id>record-info</tab-id>
            <tab-id>mads</tab-id>
        </item>
        <item xml:id="hint-code_area">
            <help>
                <p> Name of a non-jurisdictional geographic entity. </p>
            </help>
            <local-name>area</local-name>
            <tab-id>subject</tab-id>
        </item>
        <item xml:id="hint-code_authority">
            <help>
                <p> The name of the authoritative list for a controlled value is recorded here. An
                    authority field is used to indicate that a field has been entered by reference
                    to a record in an authority file. If you are not using an authority file, leave
                    this field blank. </p>
            </help>
            <local-name>authority</local-name>
            <tab-id>title</tab-id>
            <tab-id>name</tab-id>
            <tab-id>origin</tab-id>
            <tab-id>physical-description</tab-id>
            <tab-id>target-audience</tab-id>
            <tab-id>language</tab-id>
            <tab-id>subject</tab-id>
            <tab-id>classification</tab-id>
            <tab-id>note</tab-id>
            <tab-id>location</tab-id>
            <tab-id>record-info</tab-id>
        </item>
        <item xml:id="hint-code_classification">
            <help>
                <p> A designation applied to a resource that indicates the subject by applying a
                    formal system of coding and organising resources according to subject areas.
                    Classification contains the classification number of a resource. It may also
                    include the full call number if desired. </p>
            </help>
            <local-name>classification</local-name>
            <tab-id>classification</tab-id>
        </item>
        <item xml:id="hint-code_classification-edition">
            <help>
                <p> This field contains a designation of the edition of the particular
                    classification scheme indicated in authority for those schemes that are issued
                    in editions. </p>
            </help>
            <local-name>edition</local-name>
            <tab-id>classification</tab-id>
        </item>
        <item xml:id="hint-code_name-authority">
            <help>
                <p> The name of an authoritative list for a controlled value in Name is recorded
                    here. </p>
                <p> If you render the name as it occurs in the resource, you may leave the Authority
                    field value blank. If you normalize the name, you should indicate according to
                    which authority you are altering it. Use the value "Local" if a
                    locally-developed name authority file is used to catalogue the Name in question.
                </p>
            </help>
            <local-name>authority</local-name>
            <tab-id>name</tab-id>
            <tab-id>subject</tab-id>
            <tab-id>mads</tab-id>
        </item>
        <item xml:id="hint-code_uniform-title-authority">
            <help>
                <p> The name of the authoritative list for a uniform title is recorded here. </p>
            </help>
            <local-name>authority</local-name>
            <tab-id>title</tab-id>
            <tab-id>subject</tab-id>
        </item>
        <item xml:id="hint-code_titleInfo-authority-abbreviated">
            <help>
                <p> The name of the authoritative list for the abbreviated title is recorded here.
                </p>
            </help>
            <local-name>authority</local-name>
            <tab-id>title</tab-id>
            <tab-id>subject</tab-id>
        </item>
        <item xml:id="hint-code_authority-uri">
            <help>
                <p>A URI uniquely identifying the vocabulary from which the controlled term has been
                    selected, as assigned by the body responsible for the maintenance of the
                    vocabulary.</p>
                <p>URIs identifying authorities may or may not be dereferenceable to human- or
                    machine-readable information on the authority file, controlled vocabulary, or
                    thesaurus.</p>
            </help>
            <local-name>authorityURI</local-name>
            <tab-id>title</tab-id>
            <tab-id>name</tab-id>
            <tab-id>origin</tab-id>
            <tab-id>physical-description</tab-id>
            <tab-id>target-audience</tab-id>
            <tab-id>language</tab-id>
            <tab-id>subject</tab-id>
            <tab-id>classification</tab-id>
            <tab-id>genre</tab-id>
            <tab-id>location</tab-id>
            <tab-id>record-info</tab-id>
        </item>
        <item xml:id="hint-code_cartographics">
            <help>
                <p> Cartographics is a wrapper field that includes cartographic data indicating
                    spatial coverage. </p>
            </help>
            <local-name>cartographics</local-name>
            <tab-id>subject</tab-id>
        </item>
        <item xml:id="hint-code_city">
            <help>
                <p> Name of an inhabited place incorporated as a city, town, etc. </p>
            </help>
            <local-name>city</local-name>
            <tab-id>subject</tab-id>
        </item>
        <item xml:id="hint-code_citySection">
            <help>
                <p> Name of a smaller unit within a populated place, e.g., neighborhoods, parks or
                    streets. </p>
            </help>
            <local-name>citySection</local-name>
            <tab-id>subject</tab-id>
        </item>
        <item xml:id="hint-code_continent">
            <help>
                <p> Includes Asia, Africa, Europe, North America, South America.</p>
            </help>
            <local-name>continent</local-name>
            <tab-id>subject</tab-id>
        </item>
        <item xml:id="hint-code_coordinates">
            <help>
                <p> Coordinates contains a statement of coordinates covered by the resource. One or
                    more statements may be supplied. If one is supplied, it is a point (i.e., a
                    single location); if two, it is a line; if more than two, it is a n-sided
                    polygon where n=number of coordinates assigned. No three points should be
                    co-linear, and coordinates should be supplied in polygon-traversal order. </p>
            </help>
            <local-name>coordinates</local-name>
            <tab-id>subject</tab-id>
        </item>
        <item xml:id="hint-code_copyrightDate-compact">
            <help>
                <p> Note in Copyright Date the year in which copyright was claimed for the resource. </p>
                <p> Copyright Date is typically found on the page following the title page. It
                    occurs in connection with a copyright symbol, (c) or ©.</p>
                <p> If there are several copyright dates, choose the last one.</p>
                <p> If there is a Date of Issue, use it; otherwise use the Date of Copyright.</p>
                <p> If you wish to record a span of time, e.g. 1912-1914, repeat the Date of
                    Publication field. The field Point will appear.</p>
                <p> Choose "start" in one Point and "end" in the other, and enter the appropriate
                    dates in the corresponding two fields. </p>
                <p> If no Point is specified a year noted in Copyright Date is assumed to be a
                    single year. </p>
            </help>
            <local-name>copyrightDate</local-name>
            <tab-id>compact-a</tab-id>
            <tab-id>compact-b-edited-volume</tab-id>
            <tab-id>compact-b-xlink</tab-id>
            <tab-id>compact-b-review</tab-id>
        </item>
        <item xml:id="hint-code_copyrightDate">
            <help>
                <p> A date in which a resource is copyrighted. </p>
                <p> If there are several copyright dates, choose the last one.</p>
            </help>
            <local-name>copyrightDate</local-name>
            <tab-id>origin</tab-id>
        </item>
        <item xml:id="hint-code_country">
            <help>
                <p> Name of a country, i.e. a political entity considered a country. </p>
            </help>
            <local-name>country</local-name>
            <tab-id>subject</tab-id>
        </item>
        <item xml:id="hint-code_county">
            <help>
                <p> Name of the largest local administrative unit in various countries, e.g.
                    England. </p>
            </help>
            <local-name>county</local-name>
            <tab-id>subject</tab-id>
        </item>
        <item xml:id="hint-code_dateCaptured">
            <help>
                <p> The date on which a digital resource was digitized or a subsequent snapshot was
                    taken. </p>
            </help>
            <local-name>dateCaptured</local-name>
            <tab-id>origin</tab-id>
        </item>
        <item xml:id="hint-code_dateCreated">
            <help>
                <p> The date of creation of the resource. </p>
            </help>
            <local-name>dateCreated</local-name>
            <tab-id>origin</tab-id>
        </item>
        <item xml:id="hint-code_dateIssued-compact">
            <help>
                <p> Note in Date of Issue the year in which the resource was issued. </p>
                <p> The Date of Issue is typically found on the title page, in connection with place
                    of publication and publisher. </p>
                <p> The Date of Copyright is typically found on the reverse the title page, in
                    connection the © or (c) symbol.</p>
                <p> If there is a Date of Issue, use it; otherwise use the Date of Copyright.</p>
                <p> In case of periodicals, use the year that the volume or issue belongs to, rather
                    than the actual year that the periodical was physically published. This year is
                    noted as Date of Issue.</p>
                <p> If the publication spans several years, e.g. 1912-1914, repeat the date field,
                    if it is not already repeated.</p>
                <p> The field Point will appear. Choose "start" in one Point and "end" in the other,
                    and enter the appropriate dates in the corresponding two fields. </p>
                <p> If no Point is specified a year noted in date is assumed to be a single year.
                </p>
            </help>
            <local-name>dateIssued</local-name>
            <tab-id>compact-a</tab-id>
            <tab-id>compact-b-edited-volume</tab-id>
            <tab-id>compact-b-review</tab-id>
            <tab-id>compact-b-xlink</tab-id>
        </item>
        <item xml:id="hint-code_dateIssued">
            <help>
                <p> The date that the resource was published, released, or issued. </p>
                <p> The Date of Issue is typically found on the title page, in connection with place
                    of publication and publisher. </p>
                <p> The Date of Copyright is typically found on the reverse the title page, in
                    connection the © or (c) symbol.</p>
                <p> If there is a Date of Issue, use it; otherwise use the Date of Copyright.</p>
                <p> Use Point if you wish to record a span of time, e.g. 1912-1914. The values
                    "start" and "end" are used with Point. Repeat the Date of Issue field and choose
                    "start" in one and "end" in the other repetition, and enter the appropriate
                    dates in the two Date of Issue fields. </p>
                <p> If no point is specified a year noted in Date of Issue is assumed to be a single
                    year. </p>
            </help>
            <local-name>dateIssued</local-name>
            <tab-id>origin</tab-id>
        </item>
        <item xml:id="hint-code_dateModified">
            <help>
                <p> The date in which a resource is modified or changed. </p>
            </help>
            <local-name>dateModified</local-name>
            <tab-id>origin</tab-id>
        </item>
        <item xml:id="hint-code_dateOther">
            <help>
                <p> A date that does not fall into another category but is important to record. </p>
            </help>
            <local-name>dateOther</local-name>
            <tab-id>origin</tab-id>
        </item>
        <item xml:id="hint-code_dateValid">
            <help>
                <p> A date in which the content of a resource is valid. </p>
            </help>
            <local-name>dateValid</local-name>
            <tab-id>origin</tab-id>
        </item>
        <item xml:id="hint-code_description">
            <help>
                <p>Description contains a textual description for a name when this is necessary, for
                    example, to distinguish it from other names.</p>
            </help>
            <local-name>description</local-name>
            <tab-id>name</tab-id>
            <tab-id>mads</tab-id>
        </item>
        <item xml:id="hint-code_name-displayForm">
            <help>
                <p>The Display Form field makes it possible to display personal names in
                    unstructured form. It typically renders a name as given on the resource. </p>
                <p> For some applications, contractual agreements require that the form of the name
                    provided on the resource be provided.</p>
            </help>
            <local-name>displayForm</local-name>
            <tab-id>name</tab-id>
            <tab-id>mads</tab-id>
        </item>
        <item xml:id="hint-code_displayLabel">
            <help>
                <p> Display Label is used when additional text associated with a field is needed for
                    display. </p>
                <p> Display Label may be used whenever appropriate to indicate the preferred
                    labeling when displayed. Include the text preferred and capitalisation, but do
                    not include delimiters such as colons. </p>
            </help>
            <local-name>displayLabel</local-name>
            <tab-id>title</tab-id>
            <tab-id>name</tab-id>
            <tab-id>origin</tab-id>
            <tab-id>part</tab-id>
            <tab-id>physical-description</tab-id>
            <tab-id>target-audience</tab-id>
            <tab-id>language</tab-id>
            <tab-id>type</tab-id>
            <tab-id>genre</tab-id>
            <tab-id>subject</tab-id>
            <tab-id>abstract</tab-id>
            <tab-id>classification</tab-id>
            <tab-id>table-of-contents</tab-id>
            <tab-id>note</tab-id>
            <tab-id>identifier</tab-id>
            <tab-id>access-condition</tab-id>
            <tab-id>location</tab-id>
            <tab-id>record-info</tab-id>
            <tab-id>mads</tab-id>
            <tab-id>related</tab-id>
            <tab-id>related-abbreviated</tab-id>
            <tab-id>related-xlink</tab-id>
        </item>
        <item xml:id="hint-code_eventType">
            <help>
                <p>Information regarding whether the Origin Information relates to the production,
                    publication, distribution, manufacture, etc. of the resource.</p>
            </help>
            <local-name>eventType</local-name>
            <tab-id>origin</tab-id>
        </item>
        <item xml:id="hint-code_edition">
            <help>
                <p> Information identifying the version of the resource. Resources that constitute
                    the same edition generally embody essentially the same content. If no edition
                    statement applies to the resource, leave Edition empty. </p>
            </help>
            <local-name>edition</local-name>
            <tab-id>origin</tab-id>
        </item>
        <item xml:id="hint-code_date-encoding">
            <help>
                <p> Dates can be expressed in several different formats. The following values are
                    used with the Encoding: w3cdtf, iso8601, marc. The recommended encoding is
                    w3cdtf. </p>
                <p> In all three encodings, a specific year (e.g. "1938") is encoded in the same
                    way; the three standards differ in how to encode time points of time year.
                    According to w3cdtf dates follow the pattern: YYYY-MM-DD, i.e. with dashes
                    between year, month and day, and with all years have four, all months two and
                    all days two digits. If hours, minutes, and seconds are needed, the following
                    pattern is used: YYYY-MM-DDThh:mm:ss. </p>
                <p> If Encoding is not given any value, the input is assumed to be textual. This
                    means that any way of noting time can be used. If possible, use a coded value.
                </p>
            </help>
            <local-name>encoding</local-name>
            <tab-id>origin</tab-id>
            <tab-id>part</tab-id>
            <tab-id>related</tab-id>
            <tab-id>related-abbreviated</tab-id>
            <tab-id>related-xlink</tab-id>
        </item>
        <item xml:id="hint-code_temporal-encoding">
            <help>
                <p> Encoding is used to note the encoding followed in the date notation.</p>
                <p>The recommendation is to use the w3cdtf encoding. According to this encoding,
                    dates are formatted in the following way: <ul>
                        <li>Year: YYYY (e.g. 1997)</li>
                        <li>Year and month: YYYY-MM (e.g. 1997-07)</li>
                        <li>Complete date: YYYY-MM-DD (e.g. 1997-07-16)</li>
                    </ul>
                </p>
                <p>For more options, use the Extended Date-Time Format
                    (http://www.loc.gov/standards/datetime/).</p>
                <p>If you are inputting a controlled subject term such as the designation of a
                    period or an era, select "text". </p>
            </help>
            <local-name>encoding</local-name>
            <tab-id>compact-c</tab-id>
            <tab-id>compact-d</tab-id>
            <tab-id>subject</tab-id>
        </item>
        <item xml:id="hint-code_extension">
            <help>
                <p>In Extension you have access to a number of fields that we have added to the MODS
                    schema.</p>
                <p>If the record you are viewing has not been made with Tamboti, it may not have
                    Extension - at least it does not have our Extension. If it lacks Extension, you
                    can add it by using the button below.</p>
                <p>If you change the values of the fields Publication Type and Transliteration of
                    Resource, parts of the Basic Input Forms will display differently in accordance
                    with your choice.</p>
            </help>
            <local-name>extension</local-name>
            <tab-id>extension</tab-id>
        </item>
        <item xml:id="hint-code_cataloging-stage">
            <help>
                <p>Use a number from 1 to 5 to indicate how complete the record is.</p>
            </help>
            <local-name>catalogingStage</local-name>
            <tab-id>extension</tab-id>
        </item>
        <item xml:id="hint-code_extent">
            <help>
                <p> A statement of the number and specific material of the units of the resource
                    that express physical extent. A typical entry for a book might read "xiv, 213
                    p." A typical entry for a video might read "21 min." </p>
                <p> Extent may be used with electronic resources, e.g. digitised collection of
                    slides, to show how many slides constitute the resource. </p>
            </help>
            <local-name>extent</local-name>
            <tab-id>part</tab-id>
            <tab-id>related</tab-id>
            <tab-id>related-abbreviated</tab-id>
            <tab-id>related-xlink</tab-id>
            <tab-id>physical-description</tab-id>
        </item>
        <item xml:id="hint-code_extent-compact">
            <help>
                <p> The number of units and the material of the units of the resource that express
                    physical extent. Typical entries for a book might read "xiv, 213 p.", "21 p. :
                    ill", "2 v.", " 3, 5, 697 p". Use 'p.' for page, 'v.' for volume and 'ill.' for
                    illustrations.</p>
                <p> Extent may be used with other resources than paper publications. Supply
                    appropriate units (not necessarily abbreviated) depending on the nature of the
                    resource.</p>
                <p> Note that the values are not analysed into separate fields, but written as a
                    text string. The field is text-only and there are no more input options.</p>
                <p> One could enter these values in other languages and scripts than English and
                    Latin, but this is not recommended.</p>
            </help>
            <local-name>extent</local-name>
            <tab-id>compact-a</tab-id>
            <tab-id>compact-b-edited-volume</tab-id>
            <tab-id>compact-b-review</tab-id>
            <tab-id>compact-b-xlink</tab-id>
        </item>
        <item xml:id="hint-code_part-text">
            <help>
                <p> Use this subfield to record information in textual form. Use this subfield when
                    other subfields will not capture the appropriate information. </p>
            </help>
            <local-name>text</local-name>
            <tab-id>part</tab-id>
            <tab-id>related</tab-id>
            <tab-id>related-abbreviated</tab-id>
            <tab-id>related-xlink</tab-id>
        </item>
        <item xml:id="hint-code_part-text-type">
            <help>
                <p>Identifies the type of part.</p>
                <p>There is no controlled list of part types.</p>
            </help>
            <local-name>type</local-name>
            <tab-id>part</tab-id>
            <tab-id>related</tab-id>
            <tab-id>related-abbreviated</tab-id>
            <tab-id>related-xlink</tab-id>
        </item>
        <item xml:id="hint-code_typeOfResource">
            <help>
                <p> A term that specifies the characteristics and general type of the content of the
                    resource being catalogued. This field includes a high-level type that
                    categorizes the material in a general way. More specific typing is done in the
                    Genre field. </p>
                <p> Information in Type Of Resource is about the original item. For example, in the
                    case of a digitized photograph, Type Of Resource would apply to the analog
                    original; in born-digital materials, it wouldapply to the original digital
                    format. </p>
                <p> Resource Type, Genre, and Form (under Physical Description) overlap to some
                    extent. </p>
                <p> There may be no value given for Type Of Resource if the Collection or Manuscript
                    field is used and none of the enumerated values is appropriate. </p>
            </help>
            <local-name>type</local-name>
            <tab-id>type</tab-id>
        </item>
        <item xml:id="hint-code_typeOfResource-collection">
            <help>
                <p> "Yes" indicates that the resource is a collection. </p>
                <p> A collection is defined as a multi-part group of resources. One example would be
                    an anthology. If there are multiple resource types within the collection, these
                    should be enumerated in separate Type Of Resource fields. </p>
                <p> Collection and Manuscript are associated with a specific value used in Type Of
                    Resource. </p>
                <p> For example, an object which consists of a collection of maps with associated
                    text would be represented by two instances of Type Of Resource. The first would
                    be "Cartographic" with Collection "yes," and the second would be "Text" with
                    Collection "No". </p>
            </help>
            <local-name>type</local-name>
            <tab-id>type</tab-id>
        </item>
        <item xml:id="hint-code_typeOfResource-manuscript">
            <help>
                <p> "Yes" indicates that the resource is handwritten or typescript. </p>
                <p> The fields "collection" and "manuscript" are associated with a specific value
                    used in Type Of Resource. </p>
                <p> For example, an object which consists of a collection of maps with associated
                    text would be represented by two instances of Type Of Resource. </p>
                <p> The first would be "Cartographic" with Collection "yes," and the second would be
                    "text" with Collection "No". </p>
            </help>
            <local-name>type</local-name>
            <tab-id>type</tab-id>
        </item>
        <item xml:id="hint-code_part-extent-unit">
            <help>
                <p> Suggested values include page, minute, etc.
                    <!--NB: make code table with open selection?-->
                </p>
            </help>
            <local-name>unit</local-name>
            <tab-id>part</tab-id>
            <tab-id>related</tab-id>
            <tab-id>related-abbreviated</tab-id>
            <tab-id>related-xlink</tab-id>
            <tab-id>physical-description</tab-id>
            <tab-id>compact-b-article</tab-id>
            <tab-id>compact-a</tab-id>
            <tab-id>compact-b-edited-volume</tab-id>
            <tab-id>compact-b-newspaper-article</tab-id>
            <tab-id>compact-b-xlink</tab-id>
            <tab-id>compact-b-review</tab-id>
        </item>
        <item xml:id="hint-code_part-extent-start">
            <help>
                <p> Contains the beginning unit of the extent within a part (e.g., first page). </p>
            </help>
            <local-name>start</local-name>
            <tab-id>part</tab-id>
            <tab-id>related</tab-id>
            <tab-id>related-abbreviated</tab-id>
            <tab-id>related-xlink</tab-id>
        </item>
        <item xml:id="hint-code_part-extent-end">
            <help>
                <p> Contains the ending unit of the extent within a part. </p>
            </help>
            <local-name>end</local-name>
            <tab-id>part</tab-id>
            <tab-id>related</tab-id>
            <tab-id>related-abbreviated</tab-id>
            <tab-id>related-xlink</tab-id>
        </item>
        <item xml:id="hint-code_part-extent-total">
            <help>
                <p> Contains the total number of units within a part, rather than specific units.
                </p>
            </help>
            <local-name>total</local-name>
            <tab-id>part</tab-id>
            <tab-id>related</tab-id>
            <tab-id>related-abbreviated</tab-id>
            <tab-id>related-xlink</tab-id>
        </item>
        <item xml:id="hint-code_part-extent-list">
            <help>
                <p> Contains a textual listing of the units within a part (e.g., "pp. 5-9".) </p>
            </help>
            <local-name>total</local-name>
            <tab-id>part</tab-id>
            <tab-id>related</tab-id>
            <tab-id>related-abbreviated</tab-id>
            <tab-id>related-xlink</tab-id>
        </item>
        <item xml:id="hint-code_part-date">
            <help>
                <p> Date contains date information relevant to the part described. </p>
            </help>
            <local-name>date</local-name>
            <tab-id>part</tab-id>
            <tab-id>related</tab-id>
            <tab-id>related-abbreviated</tab-id>
            <tab-id>related-xlink</tab-id>
        </item>
        <item xml:id="hint-code_extraterrestrialArea">
            <help>
                <p> Name of any extraterrestrial entity or space, including solar systems, galaxies,
                    star systems, and planets as well as geographic features of individual planets.
                </p>
            </help>
            <local-name>extraterrestrialArea</local-name>
            <tab-id>subject</tab-id>
        </item>
        <item xml:id="hint-code_frequency">
            <help>
                <p> Frequency is used to note the publication pattern of the item. It is only used
                    if the Issuance of the resource is "continuing".</p>
            </help>
            <local-name>frequency</local-name>
            <tab-id>origin</tab-id>
        </item>
        <item xml:id="hint-code_genre">
            <help>
                <p> One or more terms that characterise the resource as having a particular style,
                    form, or content, such as artistic, musical, literary composition, etc. </p>
                <p> Genre contains terms that give more specificity than the broad terms used in
                    Type Of Resource. </p>
                <p> If used in connection with a digital resource, Genre should be used to
                    characterise the content of the digital resource rather than the digital
                    resource itself. </p>
                <p>The values should be chosen from a controlled vocabulary appropriate for the
                    resource described. This source vocabulary should be indicated using the
                    authority field. </p>
                <p> Genre is a term that carries different specific meanings within different
                    communities of practice, and the content of most information objects can be
                    characterised by genre at different levels of granularity, either very broad or
                    quite specific. For example, photographs and ambrotypes are both valid genre
                    characterizations, depending on your perspective, for a specific type of direct
                    positive photographic print. At the very least, provide a very broad genre term
                    for materials being digitised.</p>
                <p>Type of Resource, Genre, Form under Physical Description overlap to some degree.
                </p>
            </help>
            <local-name>genre</local-name>
            <tab-id>subject</tab-id>
            <tab-id>genre</tab-id>
        </item>
        <item xml:id="hint-code_geographic">
            <help>
                <p> Use here standard names for geographical places.</p>
                <p> Add as many Place fields as you need.</p>
                <p> The relation between the different fields is not specified, but one may start
                    with more inclusive places and move down to more restricted terms, within the
                    same Subject.</p>
                <p> If the geographic name is part of a corporate body (for example, United States.
                    Senate), it is coded as Name, not Geographic.</p>
                <p> More input options can be accessed by clicking the Subjects tab on Content
                    Description Forms. Here it is e.g. possible to parse geographic subject within
                    the Hierarchical Geographic field.</p>
            </help>
            <local-name>geographic</local-name>
            <tab-id>compact-c</tab-id>
            <tab-id>compact-d</tab-id>
            <tab-id>subject</tab-id>
        </item>
        <item xml:id="hint-code_geographicCode">
            <help>
                <p>Geographic Code includes a geographic area code associated with a resource. A
                    geographic code that represents the same entity as a term in Geographic is
                    included within the same Subject field.</p>
            </help>
            <local-name>geographicCode</local-name>
            <parent>subject</parent>
            <tab-id>subject</tab-id>
        </item>
        <item xml:id="hint-code_hierarchicalGeographic">
            <help>
                <p> This sub-field includes a hierarchical form of a place name relating to the
                    content of the resource that is both readable by humans and parsable by
                    machines. This form can be applied to the degree of specificity that is known or
                    relevant and used to generate browseable hierarchies even when values are
                    specified to different levels. Explicit inclusion of the complete hierarchy is
                    of potential benefit for automated consultation of a gazetteer to derive map
                    coordinates or to support a map-based interface for searching by country or
                    state. This sub-field has no fields. </p>
            </help>
            <local-name>hierarchicalGeographic</local-name>
            <parent>subject</parent>
            <tab-id>subject</tab-id>
        </item>
        <item xml:id="hint-code_ID">
            <help>
                <p> ID is used to link among records inside the database and to reference a field
                    inside the database from outside the database. </p>
            </help>
            <local-name>ID</local-name>
            <tab-id>name</tab-id>
            <tab-id>title</tab-id>
            <tab-id>part</tab-id>
            <tab-id>physical-description</tab-id>
            <tab-id>mads</tab-id>
            <tab-id>note</tab-id>
            <tab-id>subject</tab-id>
            <tab-id>location</tab-id>
            <tab-id>related</tab-id>
            <tab-id>related-abbreviated</tab-id>
            <tab-id>related-xlink</tab-id>
        </item>
        <item xml:id="hint-code_part-type">
            <help>
                <p> A designation of a document segment type. Suggested values include series (of a
                    periodical), volume, issue, chapter, section, paragraph, and track. Other values
                    may be used as needed. </p>
                <p> Since there is not a controlled set of terms for type, if used, the value should
                    be expressed clearly and be generally understandable. </p>
            </help>
            <local-name>type</local-name>
            <parent>part</parent>
            <tab-id>part</tab-id>
            <tab-id>related</tab-id>
            <tab-id>related-abbreviated</tab-id>
            <tab-id>related-xlink</tab-id>
        </item>
        <item xml:id="hint-code_part-detail-number">
            <help>
                <p> Contains the actual number within the part. </p>
                <p>Numbering can be sequencing in any form, e.g., Part 1, Supplement A, Book
                    Two.</p>
                <p> Text can be used as well as digits.</p>
            </help>
            <local-name>number</local-name>
            <tab-id>part</tab-id>
            <tab-id>related</tab-id>
            <tab-id>related-abbreviated</tab-id>
            <tab-id>related-xlink</tab-id>
        </item>
        <!--tab-id checked above-->
        <item xml:id="hint-code_part-detail-caption">
            <help>
                <p> Contains the caption describing the enumeration within a part. This may be the
                    same as type, but conveys what is on the item being described. </p>
                <p> Text can be used as well as digits.</p>
            </help>
            <hint/>
            <local-name>caption</local-name>
            <tab-id>part</tab-id>
            <tab-id>related</tab-id>
            <tab-id>related-abbreviated</tab-id>
            <tab-id>related-xlink</tab-id>
        </item>
        <item xml:id="hint-code_part-detail-title">
            <help>
                <p> Contains the title of the part. Only include if this is different than the Title
                    in Title Information. </p>
            </help>
            <hint/>
            <value>part-detail-title</value>
            <local-name>title</local-name>
            <parent/>
            <tab-id>part</tab-id>
            <tab-id>related</tab-id>
            <tab-id>related-abbreviated</tab-id>
            <tab-id>related-xlink</tab-id>
        </item>
        <item xml:id="hint-code_part-detail">
            <help>
                <p> Use Detail to indicate the numbering and type of designation of the part in
                    relation to the parent item.</p>
                <p> Detail contains the numbering and type of designation of the part in relation to
                    the host/parent item in which a host item resides. </p>
            </help>
            <hint/>
            <value>part-detail</value>
            <local-name>detail</local-name>
            <parent/>
            <tab-id>part</tab-id>
            <tab-id>related</tab-id>
            <tab-id>related-abbreviated</tab-id>
            <tab-id>related-xlink</tab-id>
        </item>
        <item xml:id="hint-code_part-detail-type">
            <help>
                <p> Use this field to indicate the type of the part described. </p>
                <p>Suggested values include part, volume, issue, chapter, section, paragraph, track.
                    Other values may be used as needed. However, since there is not a controlled set
                    of terms for type, if used, the value should be expressed clearly and be
                    generally understandable outside of the local context of the resource.
                    <!--NB: make open selection with code table?-->
                </p>
            </help>
            <hint/>
            <value>part-detail-type</value>
            <local-name>type</local-name>
            <parent/>
            <tab-id>part</tab-id>
            <tab-id>related</tab-id>
            <tab-id>related-abbreviated</tab-id>
            <tab-id>related-xlink</tab-id>
        </item>
        <item xml:id="hint-code_part-order">
            <help>
                <p> An integer that designates the sequence of parts. </p>
            </help>
            <hint/>
            <value>part-order</value>
            <local-name>order</local-name>
            <parent/>
            <tab-id>part</tab-id>
            <tab-id>related</tab-id>
            <tab-id>related-abbreviated</tab-id>
            <tab-id>related-xlink</tab-id>
        </item>
        <item xml:id="hint-code_part-detail-level">
            <help>
                <p> Describes the level of numbering in the host/parent item. This is used to ensure
                    that the numbering is retained in the proper order. An example is: "v. 2, no.
                    3", where the first value would have level 1 and the second level 2. </p>
            </help>
            <hint/>
            <value>part-level</value>
            <local-name>level</local-name>
            <parent/>
            <tab-id>part</tab-id>
            <tab-id>related</tab-id>
            <tab-id>related-abbreviated</tab-id>
            <tab-id>related-xlink</tab-id>
        </item>
        <item xml:id="hint-code_isbn">
            <help>
                <p>Enter here primarily the International Standard Book Number (ISBN) number of the
                    book you are cataloguing or its Digital Object Identifier (DOI). </p>
                <p>Use the 13-digit version of the ISBN number, if available.</p>
                <p>If you have access to another unique identifier, please record it.</p>
            </help>
            <value>isbn</value>
            <local-name>identifier</local-name>
            <parent/>
            <tab-id>compact-b-review</tab-id>
            <tab-id>compact-b-xlink</tab-id>
        </item>
        <item xml:id="hint-code_identifier">
            <help>
                <p> For books, enter here primarily the International Standard Book Number (ISBN) of
                    the book you are cataloguing or its Digital Object Identifier (DOI). </p>
                <p> Use the 13-digit version of the ISBN number, if available.</p>
                <p> For periodicals, enter here primarily the International Standard Serial Number
                    (ISSN) number of the periodical you are cataloguing and/or its Digital Object
                    Identifier (DOI). </p>
                <p> For articles in periodicals, enter here primarily the Digital Object Identifier
                    (DOI). </p>
                <p> If you have access to any other unique identifier, please record it by choosing
                    its Type.</p>
                <p>The identifier element should refer to the digital resource being described or to
                    its analog equivalent. The identifier should identify the object universally;
                    local call numbers or other identifiers, therefore, are not generally suitable.
                </p>
            </help>
            <value>identifier</value>
            <local-name>identifier</local-name>
            <parent/>
            <tab-id>compact-a</tab-id>
            <tab-id>compact-b-article</tab-id>
            <tab-id>compact-b-newspaper-article</tab-id>
            <tab-id>compact-b-edited-volume</tab-id>
            <tab-id>compact-b-monograph</tab-id>
            <tab-id>identifier</tab-id>
        </item>
        <item xml:id="hint-code_internetMediaType-compact">
            <help>
                <p>Use this field if the resource is electronic. </p>
                <p>Internet Media Type specifies the electronic format type of the resource, such as
                    text/html, PDF file, JPEG image or executable application.</p>
            </help>
            <hint/>
            <value>internetMediaType-compact</value>
            <local-name>internetMediaType</local-name>
            <parent/>
            <tab-id>compact-a</tab-id>
            <tab-id>compact-b-review</tab-id>
            <tab-id>compact-b-xlink</tab-id>
        </item>
        <item xml:id="hint-code_internetMediaType">
            <help>
                <p>Use this field if the resource is electronic. </p>
                <p>Internet Media Type contains an identification of the electronic format type, or
                    the data representation of the resource.</p>
                <p>Internet Media Type specifies the electronic format type, such as text/html,
                    ASCII, Postscript file, executable application or JPEG image. </p>
                <p>The Internet Media Type value is generally taken from a controlled list,
                    especially from the Internet Media types (MIME types) (see:
                    www.iana.org/assignments/media-types/index.html for a complete list).</p>
            </help>
            <hint/>
            <value>internetMediaType</value>
            <local-name>internetMediaType</local-name>
            <parent>physicalDescription</parent>
            <tab-id>physical-description</tab-id>
        </item>
        <item xml:id="hint-code_identifier-invalid">
            <help>
                <p> This field signifies a canceled or invalid identifier. It should be used with
                    the value Yes. This value is used only when recording a canceled or invalid
                    identifier. If Invalid= "Yes" is not present, the identifier is assumed to be
                    valid. </p>
            </help>
            <value>identifier-invalid</value>
            <local-name>invalid</local-name>
            <parent/>
            <tab-id>identifier</tab-id>
        </item>
        <item xml:id="hint-code_island">
            <help>
                <p> Name of a tract of land surrounded by water and smaller than a continent but is
                    not itself a separate country. </p>
            </help>
            <value>genre</value>
            <local-name>island</local-name>
            <parent>hierarchicalGeographic</parent>
            <tab-id>subject</tab-id>
        </item>
        <item xml:id="hint-code_issuance">
            <help>
                <p> In Issuance one records how the resource is issued. It may be used with the
                    following values: continuing and monographic. </p>
                <p> A continuing resource is issued over time with no predetermined conclusion.
                    Continuing resources include serials/periodicals and ongoing integrating
                    resources, i.e. those that are continuously updated. A monographic resource is
                    either complete in one part or intended to be completed in a finite number of
                    separate parts. </p>
            </help>
            <hint/>
            <value>issuance</value>
            <local-name>issuance</local-name>
            <parent/>
            <tab-id>origin</tab-id>
        </item>
        <item xml:id="hint-code_keyDate">
            <help>
                <p> One can record different events that may be important in the life of a resource
                    in a number of different date fields. When multiple date fields apply but would
                    contain identical data, one may choose to use only one of the relevant date
                    fields. In this case, mark one and only one such date field as a key date by
                    choosing "date is key date" in Key Date. </p>
            </help>
            <value>keyDate</value>
            <local-name>keyDate</local-name>
            <parent/>
            <tab-id>origin</tab-id>
            <tab-id>subject</tab-id>
        </item>
        <item xml:id="hint-code_lang">
            <help>
                <p> The language used within the input field is specified here, if this language is
                    different from the language noted in Language of Resource. </p>
                <p>The most common languages have been moved to the top of the list. </p>
            </help>
            <hint/>
            <value>lang</value>
            <local-name>lang</local-name>
            <parent/>
            <tab-id>compact-a</tab-id>
            <tab-id>name</tab-id>
            <tab-id>title</tab-id>
            <tab-id>origin</tab-id>
            <tab-id>part</tab-id>
            <tab-id>related</tab-id>
            <tab-id>related-abbreviated</tab-id>
            <tab-id>related-xlink</tab-id>
            <tab-id>physical-description</tab-id>
            <tab-id>access-condition</tab-id>
            <tab-id>language</tab-id>
            <tab-id>genre</tab-id>
            <tab-id>location</tab-id>
            <tab-id>mads</tab-id>
            <tab-id>note</tab-id>
            <tab-id>subject</tab-id>
            <tab-id>record-info</tab-id>
        </item>
        <item xml:id="hint-code_lang-global-compact">
            <help>
                <p> The language used within Title Information is specified here. The most common
                    languages have been moved to the top of the list. </p>
                <p>The language noted here is the language chosen when the record was created. It
                    applies to the record as a whole, unless otherwise noted. Since a title or a
                    name as a subject can be in any language, the Global Language can be overruled
                    here by choosing a Local Language.</p>
            </help>
            <hint/>
            <value>lang-global-compact</value>
            <local-name>lang</local-name>
            <parent/>
            <tab-id>compact-d</tab-id>
        </item>
        <item xml:id="hint-code_lang-local-compact">
            <help>
                <p> The language used within Title Information is specified here. The most common
                    languages have been moved to the top of the list. </p>
                <p>The language noted here is not the language chosen when the record was created.
                    The language noted here only applies to the field(s) immediately below. Since a
                    title or a name as a subject can be in any language , the Global Language can be
                    overruled here by choosing a Local Language.</p>
            </help>
            <hint/>
            <value>lang-local-compact</value>
            <local-name>lang</local-name>
            <parent/>
            <tab-id>compact-d</tab-id>
        </item>
        <item xml:id="hint-code_name-lang">
            <help>
                <p> The language used within Name Information is specified here, if this language is
                    different from the language noted in Language of Resource. The most common
                    languages have been moved to the top of the list. </p>
                <p> Language can be applied the Name as a whole. Do this if you are using only one
                    Language value for all Name Parts. If you are using different values for
                    different Name Parts, apply Language to each Name Part and leave Language empty
                    under Name as a whole. </p>
            </help>
            <hint/>
            <value>name-lang</value>
            <local-name>lang</local-name>
            <parent/>
            <tab-id>name</tab-id>
            <tab-id>identifier</tab-id>
            <tab-id>mads</tab-id>
        </item>
        <item xml:id="hint-code_namePart-lang">
            <help>
                <p>The language used within Title Information is specified here, if this language is
                    different from the language noted in Language of Resource. The most common
                    languages have been moved to the top of the list. </p>
                <p> Language can be applied the Name as a whole. Do this if you are using only one
                    Language value for all Name Parts. If you are using different values for
                    different Name Parts, apply Language to each Name Part and leave Language empty
                    under Name as a whole. </p>
            </help>
            <hint/>
            <value>namePart-lang</value>
            <local-name>lang</local-name>
            <parent/>
            <tab-id>name</tab-id>
            <tab-id>mads</tab-id>
        </item>
        <item xml:id="hint-code_originInfo-lang">
            <help>
                <p> The language used within Origin Information is specified here, if this language
                    is different from the language noted in Language of Resource. The most common
                    languages have been moved to the top of the list. </p>
                <p> Language can be applied the Origin Information as a whole. Do this if you are
                    using only one Language value for all Place Terms, for Publisher and for
                    Edition. If you are using different Language values inside Origin Information,
                    apply Language to each field and leave Language empty under Origin Information.
                </p>
            </help>
            <hint/>
            <value>originInfo-lang</value>
            <local-name>lang</local-name>
            <parent/>
            <tab-id>origin</tab-id>
        </item>
        <item xml:id="hint-code_language">
            <help>
                <p> Here the language of the contents of the described resource as a whole is noted. </p>
                <p> Language may also be expressed in relation to a single field, by means of the
                    Language field, in order to note the language used in a particular field. This
                    is only necessary if the language used in the field in question (e.g. in an
                    alternative title) is different from the language noted in Resource Language. </p>
                <p> Cataloging Language under Record Information is used to note the language used
                    in the record itself. Cataloging Language is not the Resource Language, but of
                    the metadata describing a resource, i.e. the record you are working on or
                    looking at now. The Language of Cataloging is assumed to be English; if you wish
                    to note another Language of Cataloging, click "Show All" to display the required
                    tab.. </p>
                <p> At least one Resource Language field is required for all resources in which
                    language is primary to understanding the resource. These resources include
                    textual resources, but also audio and video resources with spoken word
                    components. </p>
                <p> Although Language is usually not required for non-textual resources such as
                    images, it could be used effectively for such resources when language is a
                    component. Examples of the latter might include a photograph of a sign with text
                    or a monument with an inscription. </p>
                <p> The Language field is optional for resources in which language is important to
                    understanding the resource, but not primary. For example, the caption of a
                    photograph may in some instances be important to understanding the photograph,
                    but not primary. If the content of the resource is in more than one language,
                    Language is repeated for each language employed. </p>
            </help>
            <hint/>
            <value>language</value>
            <local-name>language</local-name>
            <parent/>
            <tab-id>language</tab-id>
            <tab-id>target-audience</tab-id>
            <tab-id>abstract</tab-id>
            <tab-id>classification</tab-id>
            <tab-id>table-of-contents</tab-id>
        </item>
        <item xml:id="hint-code_languageTerm">
            <help>
                <p> Language Term specifies the language(s) of the content of the resource.
                    <!--NB: revise after question of two types of input is solved.--> It may be
                    expressed in textual or coded form. If in coded form, the source of the code
                    should be indicated in the value of the authority field. If no authority is
                    given, it is assumed that the content is textual, i.e. that the Type is "text".
                    If there is more than one representation of the same language, e.g. using
                    different forms of the same language (code or text) or from different
                    authorities, Language Term is repeated within the Language container. </p>
            </help>
            <hint/>
            <value>languageTerm</value>
            <local-name>languageTerm</local-name>
            <parent>language</parent>
            <tab-id>language</tab-id>
            <tab-id>record-info</tab-id>
        </item>
        <item xml:id="hint-code_location">
            <help>
                <p> Location identifies the institution or repository holding the resource, or a
                    remote location in the form of a URL where the resource is available. In the
                    case of a physical resource, information is noted about what the institution
                    identified in Physical Location holds of the resource in question and its
                    specific location within the institution. </p>
                <p> Holdings information consists of copy-specific information about the resource,
                    information about the specific location within an institution, version
                    information, and other information that is peculiar to the institution. </p>
            </help>
            <hint/>
            <value>location</value>
            <local-name>location</local-name>
            <parent>mods</parent>
            <tab-id>location</tab-id>
        </item>
        <item xml:id="hint-code_more-related-item">
            <help>
                <p> More input options can be found on the Related Items Forms tab.</p>
            </help>
            <hint/>
            <value>more-related-item</value>
            <local-name>more</local-name>
            <parent/>
            <tab-id>compact-b-article</tab-id>
            <tab-id>compact-b-newspaper-article</tab-id>
            <tab-id>compact-b-edited-volume</tab-id>
            <tab-id>compact-b-monograph</tab-id>
            <tab-id>compact-b-review</tab-id>
            <tab-id>compact-b-xlink</tab-id>
        </item>
        <item xml:id="hint-code_more-physical-description">
            <help>
                <p> More input options can be found on the Physical Description tab on the Citation
                    Forms.</p>
            </help>
            <hint/>
            <value>more-physical-description</value>
            <local-name>more</local-name>
            <parent/>
            <tab-id>compact-a</tab-id>
        </item>
        <item xml:id="hint-code_more-location">
            <help>
                <p> More input options can be found on the Locations tab on the Remaining Forms.</p>
            </help>
            <hint/>
            <value>more-location</value>
            <local-name>more</local-name>
            <parent/>
            <tab-id>compact-a</tab-id>
            <tab-id>compact-b-review</tab-id>
            <tab-id>compact-b-xlink</tab-id>
        </item>
        <item xml:id="hint-code_more-identifier">
            <help>
                <p> More input options can be found on the Identifiers tab on the Remaining
                    Forms.</p>
            </help>
            <hint/>
            <value>more-identifier</value>
            <local-name>more</local-name>
            <parent/>
            <tab-id>compact-a</tab-id>
        </item>
        <item xml:id="hint-code_more-subjects">
            <help>
                <p> More input options can be found on the Subjects tab on Content Description
                    Forms.</p>
            </help>
            <hint/>
            <value>more-subjects</value>
            <local-name>more</local-name>
            <parent/>
            <tab-id>compact-c</tab-id>
        </item>
        <item xml:id="hint-code_more-title-information">
            <help>
                <p> More input options can be found on the Title Information tab on the Citation
                    Forms.</p>
            </help>
            <hint/>
            <value>more-title-information</value>
            <local-name>more</local-name>
            <parent/>
            <tab-id>compact-a</tab-id>
            <tab-id>compact-b-review</tab-id>
            <tab-id>compact-b-xlink</tab-id>
        </item>
        <item xml:id="hint-code_more-name-information">
            <help>
                <p> More input options can be found on the Name Information tab on the Citation
                    Forms.</p>
            </help>
            <hint/>
            <value>more-name-information</value>
            <local-name>more</local-name>
            <parent/>
            <tab-id>compact-a</tab-id>
            <tab-id>compact-b-edited-volume</tab-id>
            <tab-id>compact-b-monograph</tab-id>
            <tab-id>compact-b-review</tab-id>
            <tab-id>compact-b-xlink</tab-id>
        </item>
        <item xml:id="hint-code_more-origin-information">
            <help>
                <p> More input options can be found on the Origin Information tab on the Citation
                    Forms.</p>
            </help>
            <hint/>
            <value>more-origin-information</value>
            <local-name>more</local-name>
            <parent/>
            <tab-id>compact-a</tab-id>
            <tab-id>compact-b-edited-volume</tab-id>
            <tab-id>compact-b-edited-volume</tab-id>
        </item>
        <item xml:id="hint-code_name">
            <help>
                <p> In Names are catalogued the names of the persons, organisations, or events
                    (conferences, meetings, etc.) that are associated with the resource being
                    catalogued. These relationship between these named entities and the resource is
                    described in Role. </p>
                <p>Include as many Names blocks as needed. </p>
                <p> In addition to describing named entities associated with the creation of a
                    resource, Names is also used as a kind of Subject. For names used as subjects,
                    to note that the resource is about a named entity, see the Subjects tab. </p>
                <p> For textual materials, include the names of all known authors, translators,
                    compilers, and editors. </p>
                <p> For images, include the name of the creator of the original intellectual content
                    (the original photographer, painter, architect, etc.) and the name of anyone
                    capturing that content in a new medium (for a photograph of a building, include
                    both the architect and the photographer). </p>
                <p> If no known person or organisation etc. is known to be associated with the
                    resource, or if the person or organisation etc. is anonymous, do not use
                    "unknown," "anonymous," or similar annotations; rather, leave the Names block
                    empty. </p>
            </help>
            <hint/>
            <value>name</value>
            <local-name>name</local-name>
            <parent/>
            <tab-id>name</tab-id>
            <tab-id>mads</tab-id>
            <tab-id>subject</tab-id>
        </item>
        <item xml:id="hint-code_name-relatedItem-periodical-editor-compact">
            <help>
                <p> In Editor(s) of Periodical, catalogue the names of the institution that serves
                    as editor of the periodical.</p>
                <p> The editor of the periodical as such, not a specific issue, is recorded
                    here.</p>
                <p> Include as many editor as needed, by clicking the '+' buttons. </p>
                <p> If individual persons serve as editors, use the Citation Forms.</p>
                <p> Analyse each name into separate name parts. Record the more general designation
                    in the first field and a more specific designation in the second field. If this
                    is not possible, enter the whole name in one field.</p>
                <p> Please note that the role pertaining to a name follows the name in question.</p>
            </help>
            <hint/>
            <value>name-relatedItem-periodical-editor-compact</value>
            <local-name>name</local-name>
            <parent/>
            <tab-id>compact-b-article</tab-id>
            <tab-id>compact-b-newspaper-article</tab-id>
            <tab-id>compact-b-review</tab-id>
        </item>
        <item xml:id="hint-code_name-compact">
            <help>
                <p> In Names and Roles, catalogue the names of each person, corporation or
                    conference associated with the resource.</p>
                <p> Include as many Names and Roles as needed, by clicking the '+' button. </p>
                <p> Choose an appropriate Type of Name for each name, "personal" for personal names,
                    "corporate" for names of institutions, and "conference" for names of events such
                    as conferences. </p>
                <p> If you choose "corporate" or "conference," please clear the values "Given" and
                    "Family" in front of the name parts by choosing "(none selected)." Conversely,
                    if you add a personal name, please choose "Given Name" and "Family Name" as is
                    relevant. </p>
                <p> Given Name and Family Name can occur in any order. </p>
                <p> Please note that the role pertaining to a name follows the name in question.
                </p>
            </help>
            <hint/>
            <value>name-compact</value>
            <local-name>name</local-name>
            <parent/>
            <tab-id>compact-a</tab-id>
            <tab-id>compact-b-review</tab-id>
            <tab-id>compact-b-xlink</tab-id>
            <tab-id>compact-d</tab-id>
        </item>
        <item xml:id="hint-code_subject-name-corporate-compact">
            <help>
                <p> In Institution(s) as Topic, catalogue the names of the corporations occurring as
                    topic in the catalogued resource.</p>
                <p> Analyse each name into separate name parts. Record the more general designation
                    in the first field and a more specific designation in the second field. If this
                    is not possible, enter the whole name in one field.</p>
                <p> Include as many names of institutions as needed, by clicking the '+' button.
                </p>
            </help>
            <hint/>
            <value>subject-name-corporate-compact</value>
            <local-name>name</local-name>
            <parent/>
            <tab-id>compact-c</tab-id>
        </item>
        <item xml:id="hint-code_subject-namePart-corporate-compact">
            <help>
                <p> Analyse each name into separate name parts. Record the more general designation
                    in the first field and a more specific designation in the second field. If this
                    is not possible, enter the whole name in one field.</p>
                <p> Include as many names of institutions as needed, by clicking the '+' button.
                </p>
            </help>
            <hint/>
            <value>subject-namePart-corporate-compact</value>
            <local-name>name</local-name>
            <parent/>
            <tab-id>compact-c</tab-id>
        </item>
        <item xml:id="hint-code_relatedItem-namePart-corporate-compact">
            <help>
                <p> Analyse each name into separate name parts. Record the more general designation
                    in the first field and a more specific designation in the second field. If this
                    is not possible, enter the whole name in one field.</p>
            </help>
            <hint/>
            <value>relatedItem-namePart-corporate-compact</value>
            <local-name>name</local-name>
            <parent/>
            <tab-id>compact-b-article</tab-id>
            <tab-id>compact-b-newspaper-article</tab-id>
            <tab-id>compact-b-review</tab-id>
        </item>
        <item xml:id="hint-code_subject-name-personal-compact">
            <help>
                <p> In Person(s) as Topic, catalogue the names of the persons or corporate entities
                    that occur as topic in the work you are cataloguing.</p>
                <p> Add as many Names as needed, by clicking the '+' button. </p>
            </help>
            <hint/>
            <value>subject-name-personal-compact</value>
            <local-name>name</local-name>
            <parent/>
            <tab-id>compact-c</tab-id>
        </item>
        <item xml:id="hint-code_subject-name">
            <help>
                <p> In Persons and Institutions as Topics, catalogue the names of each person or
                    institution that serves as topic of the resource you are cataloguing. </p>
                <p> Add as many Persons and Institutions as Topics as is necessary. </p>
                <p> More input options can be accessed by clicking the Subjects tab on Content
                    Description Forms.</p>
            </help>
            <hint/>
            <value>subject-name</value>
            <local-name>name</local-name>
            <parent/>
            <tab-id>compact-c</tab-id>
            <tab-id>compact-d</tab-id>
        </item>
        <item xml:id="hint-code_subject-name-corporate">
            <help>
                <p> Analyse each name into separate name parts, e.g. Given Name and Family Name.</p>
                <p> If this is not possible, choose "(none selected)" and enter the whole name in
                    the field in question.</p>
                <p> If a given or family name consists of several parts, enter all parts of the same
                    type in the same field.</p>
                <p> More input options can be accessed by clicking the Subjects tab on Content
                    Description Forms.</p>
            </help>
            <hint/>
            <value>subject-name-corporate</value>
            <local-name>name</local-name>
            <parent/>
            <tab-id>titles</tab-id>
        </item>
        <item xml:id="hint-code_subject-name-personal">
            <help>
                <p> Analyse each name into separate name parts, e.g. Given Name and Family Name.</p>
                <p> If this is not possible, choose "(none selected)" and enter the whole name in
                    the field in question.</p>
                <p> If a given or family name consists of several parts, enter all parts of the same
                    type in the same field.</p>
                <p> More input options can be accessed by clicking the Subjects tab on Content
                    Description Forms.</p>
            </help>
            <hint/>
            <value>subject-name-personal</value>
            <local-name>name</local-name>
            <parent/>
            <tab-id>titles</tab-id>
        </item>
        <item xml:id="hint-code_edited-volume-name-compact">
            <help>
                <p> In Editors of Edited Volume, catalogue the names of each person or corporation
                    associated with the edited volume.</p>
                <p> Include as many editors as needed, by clicking the '+' buttons. </p>
                <p> More input options can be found on the Related Items Forms tab.</p>
            </help>
            <value>edited-volume-name-compact</value>
            <local-name>name</local-name>
            <parent/>
            <tab-id>compact-b-edited-volume</tab-id>
        </item>
        <item xml:id="hint-code_series-name-compact">
            <help>
                <p> In Editors of Monograph Series, catalogue the names of each person or
                    corporation associated with the monograph series.</p>
                <p> Include as many editors as needed, by clicking the '+' buttons. </p>
                <p> More input options can be found on the Related Items Forms tab.</p>
            </help>
            <value>series-name-compact</value>
            <local-name>name</local-name>
            <parent/>
            <tab-id>compact-b-monograph</tab-id>
        </item>
        <item xml:id="hint-code_namePart">
            <help>
                <p>The name itself is always entered into a Name Part. This is the case even if it
                    is not possible to parse the name into separate units.</p>
            </help>
            <hint/>
            <value>namePart</value>
            <local-name>namePart</local-name>
            <parent>name</parent>
            <tab-id>name</tab-id>
            <tab-id>mads</tab-id>
            <tab-id>subject</tab-id>
        </item>
        <item xml:id="hint-code_namePart-compact">
            <help>
                <p> Analyse each name into separate name parts.</p>
                <p> If possible, analyse each personal name into Given Name and Family Name. If this
                    is not possible, choose "(none selected)" and enter the whole name in the field
                    in question.</p>
                <p> If a given or family name consists of several parts, enter all parts of the same
                    type in the same field.</p>
                <p> If the name is a corporate name or a conference name, select "(None Selected)"
                    instead of "Given" and "Family", if necessary.</p>
                <p> Analyse each corporate name into separate name parts if it consists of several
                    components. Record the more general designation in the first field and the more
                    specific designation in the second field. If this is not possible, enter the
                    whole name in one field.</p>
                <p> If you have chosen a transliteration scheme when you created the record, you
                    will have the option of entering a transliteration.</p>
                <p> If the name is in a language that is usually transliterated, enter the
                    transliterated name parts in their respective fields. Use the transliteration
                    scheme you chose when selecting a record template. </p>
            </help>
            <hint/>
            <value>namePart-compact</value>
            <local-name>namePart</local-name>
            <parent>name</parent>
            <tab-id>compact-a</tab-id>
            <tab-id>compact-b-edited-volume</tab-id>
            <tab-id>compact-b-monograph</tab-id>
            <tab-id>compact-b-review</tab-id>
            <tab-id>compact-b-xlink</tab-id>
            <tab-id>compact-d</tab-id>
        </item>
        <item xml:id="hint-code_subject-namePart-personal-compact">
            <help>
                <p> If possible, analyse each personal name into Given Name and Family Name. If this
                    is not possible, select the Subjects tab on Content Description Forms and
                    deselect the name part type.</p>
            </help>
            <hint/>
            <value>subject-namePart-personal-compact</value>
            <local-name>namePart</local-name>
            <parent>name</parent>
            <tab-id>compact-c</tab-id>
        </item>
        <item xml:id="hint-code_namePart-institution-compact">
            <help>
                <p> Analyse each corporate name into separate name parts. Record the more general
                    designation in the first field and a more specific designation in the second
                    field. If this is not possible, enter the whole name in one field.</p>
                <p> If you have chosen a transliteration scheme when you created the record, you
                    will have the option of entering a transliteration and a translation.</p>
                <p> If the name is in a language that is usually transliterated, enter the
                    transliterated name parts in their respective fields. Use the transliteration
                    scheme you chose when selecting a record template. </p>
            </help>
            <hint/>
            <value>namePart-institution-compact</value>
            <local-name>namePart</local-name>
            <parent>name</parent>
            <tab-id>compact-b-edited-volume</tab-id>
            <tab-id>compact-b-monograph</tab-id>
        </item>
        <item xml:id="hint-code_namePart-type">
            <help>
                <p>Name Part includes each part of the name. Parsing is used to parse parts of a
                    personal name into family/surname and given name/forename, as well as terms of
                    address, but it is also used to indicate a date associated with the name and to
                    parse the parts of a corporate name. </p>
                <p> The parsing performed is indicated by the Type field. This field takes the
                    following values: Date, Family, Given, Terms Of Address. </p>
                <p> "Date" is used to note dates that are not integral parts of a name. For dates
                    within e.g. a conference name, do not use this field to separate the date, since
                    it is an integral part of the name of the conference. The birth date associated
                    with a personal name, however, is not an integral part of the name, but can be
                    added to distinguish the name from others, so it does include a separate Name
                    Part with a Type of "Date". </p>
                <p> "Family" is used for the family name or surname of a person. </p>
                <p> "Given" is used for the given name or forename of a person. </p>
                <p> "Terms Of Address" is used to record titles and enumeration associated with a
                    name, such as "Jr.", "II", etc. </p>
                <p> If you do not know how to break up a name or if a name is not constructed
                    according to the family name/given name pattern, leave the Type of the Name Part
                    blank and enter the whole name as it occurs in one Name Part. </p>
            </help>
            <hint/>
            <value>namePart-type</value>
            <local-name>namePart</local-name>
            <parent>name</parent>
            <tab-id>name</tab-id>
            <tab-id>mads</tab-id>
            <tab-id>subject</tab-id>
        </item>
        <item xml:id="hint-code_nameTitleGroup">
            <help>
                <p> Name-Title Group can be used with Name and Title Information to enable an
                    explicit link between a name and a title when that is desirable. </p>
                <p> The same value is assigned to this attribute for the two elements. This
                    attribute is used to link names to uniform titles when the name-uniform title
                    combination is an authority controlled heading. </p>
            </help>
            <hint/>
            <value>nameTitleGroup</value>
            <local-name>nameTitleGroup</local-name>
            <parent/>
            <tab-id>name</tab-id>
            <tab-id>title</tab-id>
            <tab-id>mads</tab-id>
            <tab-id>subject</tab-id>
        </item>
        <item xml:id="hint-code_nonSort">
            <help>
                <p> Non Sort contains characters, including initial articles (typically "A" and
                    "The" in English), punctuation, and spaces that appear at the beginning of a
                    title that should be ignored when indexing and sorting. </p>
                <p> Non Sort should only be used with languages that have pre-posed articles. </p>
            </help>
            <hint/>
            <value>nonSort</value>
            <local-name>nonSort</local-name>
            <parent/>
            <tab-id>compact-a</tab-id>
            <tab-id>compact-b-article</tab-id>
            <tab-id>compact-b-newspaper-article</tab-id>
            <tab-id>compact-b-review</tab-id>
            <tab-id>compact-b-xlink</tab-id>
            <tab-id>title</tab-id>
            <tab-id>subject</tab-id>
        </item>
        <item xml:id="hint-code_note">
            <help>
                <p> A note contains general information relating to a resource. </p>
                <p> Notes should be used only for information that cannot be encoded in another,
                    more specific, ways. </p>
                <p> In Type, state which aspect of the work catalogued the note relates to.</p>
                <p> In Note, you can use HTML formatting. You do this on your own risk. If your
                    markup is not well-formed XHTML, the record will be saved, but you will not be
                    able to access it through the search interface, since this only accepts
                    well-formed XHTML.</p>
                <p> For the ampersand ('&amp;'), use '&amp;#x26;'.</p>
            </help>
            <hint/>
            <value>note</value>
            <local-name>note</local-name>
            <parent/>
            <tab-id>compact-c</tab-id>
            <tab-id>compact-d</tab-id>
            <tab-id>note</tab-id>
        </item>
        <item xml:id="hint-code_physicalDescription_note">
            <help>
                <p> A designation of a particular physical presentation of a resource. Form includes
                    information that specifies the physical note or medium of material for a
                    resource. Either a controlled list of values or free text may be used. </p>
            </help>
            <hint/>
            <value>note</value>
            <local-name>note</local-name>
            <parent/>
            <tab-id>compact-c</tab-id>
            <tab-id>compact-d</tab-id>
            <tab-id>physical-description</tab-id>
            <tab-id>note</tab-id>
        </item>
        <item xml:id="hint-code_location_note">
            <help>
                <p> Note relating to a specific copy of a document. </p>
            </help>
            <hint/>
            <value>note</value>
            <local-name>note</local-name>
            <parent/>
            <tab-id>location</tab-id>
        </item>
        <item xml:id="hint-code_enumerationAndChronology">
            <help>
                <p> Alpha-numeric identification, such as a volume or issue, and an indication of
                    the date of publication or date of issue of a component of a multi-part
                    resource, distinguishing it from other components of the same resource.
                    Enumeration And Chronology is an unparsed string that comprises a summary
                    holdings statement. If more granularity is needed, a parsed statement using an
                    external schema may be used within Holdings External. </p>
            </help>
            <hint/>
            <value>note</value>
            <local-name>note</local-name>
            <parent/>
            <tab-id>location</tab-id>
        </item>
        <item xml:id="hint-code_holdingExternal">
            <help>
                <p> Holdings information that uses a schema defined externally to MODS.</p>
                <p>Holdings External may include more detailed holdings information than that
                    accommodated by the MODS schema. An example is ISO 20775 and its accompanying
                    schema. </p>
            </help>
            <hint/>
            <value>holdingExternal</value>
            <local-name>holdingExternal</local-name>
            <parent/>
            <tab-id>location</tab-id>
        </item>
        <item xml:id="hint-code_unitType">
            <help>
                <p> The category of bibliographic entity for which Enumeration And Chronology is
                    given, i.e. basic bibliographic unit, supplement, or index. </p>
            </help>
            <hint/>
            <value>note</value>
            <local-name>note</local-name>
            <parent/>
            <tab-id>location</tab-id>
        </item>
        <item xml:id="hint-code_physicalDescription_note_type">
            <help>
                <p> This field is used if desired to specify whether the note concerns materials or
                    techniques, e.g. type="material": oil paint; type="technique": painting. </p>
            </help>
            <hint/>
            <value>note</value>
            <local-name>note</local-name>
            <parent/>
            <tab-id>compact-c</tab-id>
            <tab-id>compact-d</tab-id>
            <tab-id>physical-description</tab-id>
            <tab-id>note</tab-id>
        </item>
        <item xml:id="hint-code_physicalDescription_note_authority">
            <help>
                <p> The name of the authoritative list for a controlled value is recorded here. A
                    list of authorities is maintained at:
                    www.loc.gov/marc/sourcecode/note/notesource.html. The MARC 21 form list contains
                    most of the values defined in fields 008/23 (BK, MU, CR, MX) and 008/29 (MP,
                    VM). Use authority="marcform" to indicate its use. </p>
            </help>
            <hint/>
            <value>note</value>
            <local-name>note</local-name>
            <parent/>
            <tab-id>compact-c</tab-id>
            <tab-id>compact-d</tab-id>
            <tab-id>note</tab-id>
        </item>
        <item xml:id="hint-code_objectPart">
            <help>
                <p> This field designates which part of the resource is in the language stated in
                    Language Term. The values of the field are not controlled by an authority list;
                    examples of values of Object Part are "Summary" and "Caption". If you use this
                    field, use expressions of similar generality. </p>
            </help>
            <hint/>
            <value>objectPart</value>
            <local-name>objectPart</local-name>
            <parent>language</parent>
            <tab-id>language</tab-id>
        </item>
        <item xml:id="hint-code_occupation">
            <help>
                <p> Occupation includes a term that is descriptive of the occupation reflected in
                    the contents of the described materials. It is not used to list the occupations
                    of the creators of the described materials, unless those occupations are
                    significantly reflected in the materials themselves or bear some relationship to
                    the materials. </p>
            </help>
            <value>occupation</value>
            <local-name>occupation</local-name>
            <parent>subject</parent>
            <tab-id>subject</tab-id>
        </item>
        <item xml:id="hint-code_originInfo">
            <help>
                <p> Enter here information about the publication's origin, including its place of
                    origin or publication, its publisher, and its date of issue or date of
                    copyright. </p>
                <!--expand-->
            </help>
            <hint/>
            <value>originInfo</value>
            <local-name>originInfo</local-name>
            <parent/>
            <tab-id>origin</tab-id>
        </item>
        <item xml:id="hint-code_originInfo-compact">
            <help>
                <p> Enter here information about the publication's origin, including its place of
                    origin or publication, its publisher, and its date of issue or date of
                    copyright. </p>
            </help>
            <hint/>
            <value>originInfo-compact</value>
            <local-name>originInfo</local-name>
            <parent/>
            <tab-id>compact-a</tab-id>
            <tab-id>compact-b-edited-volume</tab-id>
            <tab-id>compact-b-review</tab-id>
            <tab-id>compact-b-xlink</tab-id>
        </item>
        <item xml:id="hint-code_part-relatedItem-periodical-compact">
            <help>
                <p> For an article or a book review in a periodical, note here <ul>
                        <li>in which volume and (if relevant) which issue the article or book review
                            occurs in the periodical </li>
                        <li>in which year the volume/issue was published</li>
                        <li>on which pages the article occurs</li>
                    </ul>.</p>
                <p> For a contribution to an edited volume, note here <ul>
                        <li>in which volume the contribution occurs in the edited volume</li>
                        <li>leave volume and issue blank</li>
                        <li>on which pages the contribution occurs</li>
                    </ul>.</p>
            </help>
            <hint/>
            <value>part-relatedItem-periodical-compact</value>
            <local-name>part</local-name>
            <parent/>
            <tab-id>compact-b-article</tab-id>
            <tab-id>compact-b-newspaper-article</tab-id>
            <tab-id>compact-b-review</tab-id>
            <tab-id>compact-b-xlink</tab-id>
        </item>
        <item xml:id="hint-code_part">
            <help>
                <p> The designation of physical parts of a resource in a detailed form. Part is used
                    to provide detailed description of the physical parts of a resource. It may be
                    used as a top level field to designate the physical parts or under Related Item.
                    If used under Related Item, Part records the location of a part within a
                    host/parent item. If used as a top level field, Part records a part of a
                    resource, usually because the library is not in possession of the whole
                    resource. </p>
                <p> Use Part when the record in question refers to either a physical or structural
                    part of a resource, rather than an intellectual part. An intellectual part of a
                    resource should be recorded in various fields under Title. A newspaper issue
                    would e.g. generally be indicated with Part, rather than indicating the issue
                    number as part of the title. Other examples include an issue of a journal or a
                    single story from a collection. Part as a top level field would also be used to
                    describe one reel of microfilm in a set, or in any other case in which the part
                    being described is not an intellectual whole by itself. When in doubt, and only
                    part numbers and/or part names are needed, use Part Number and/or Part Name
                    under Title under Title Information. </p>
            </help>
            <hint/>
            <value>part</value>
            <local-name>part</local-name>
            <parent/>
            <tab-id>part</tab-id>
            <tab-id>related</tab-id>
            <tab-id>related-abbreviated</tab-id>
            <tab-id>related-xlink</tab-id>
        </item>
        <item xml:id="hint-code_other-part">
            <help>
                <p> Part is used here to record the various parts of one publication inside another
                    publication. </p>
                <p> Most publications only have one part. An article may have several instalments,
                    but most articles, contributions and book reviews are published as a whole.</p>
                <p> For articles and book reviews, the volume and issue, the year of publication and
                    the page extent are noted.</p>
                <p> For contributions to edited volumes, the volume (if relevant) and the page
                    extent are noted.</p>
            </help>
            <hint/>
            <value>other-part</value>
            <local-name>part</local-name>
            <parent/>
            <tab-id>titles</tab-id>
        </item>
        <item xml:id="hint-code_edited-volume-part-compact">
            <help>
                <p>Enter here information regarding in which volume of the edited volume the
                    contribution occurs, if the edited volume is in several volumes.</p>
                <p>Enter also information regarding the page extent of the contribution.</p>
            </help>
            <hint/>
            <value>edited-volume-part-compact</value>
            <local-name>part</local-name>
            <parent>relatedItem</parent>
            <tab-id>compact-b-edited-volume</tab-id>
        </item>
        <item xml:id="hint-code_series-part-compact">
            <help>
                <p>Enter here information regarding in which volume of the monograph series the book
                    occurs.</p>
            </help>
            <hint/>
            <value>series-part-compact</value>
            <local-name>part</local-name>
            <parent>relatedItem</parent>
            <tab-id>titles</tab-id>
            <tab-id>compact-b-monograph</tab-id>
        </item>
        <item xml:id="hint-code_partName">
            <help>
                <p> Part Name is used for a part or section name of a title. Use Part Name when a
                    part name is present, rather than including the part name in the text of Title.
                    Use Part Name to describe the section or division titles of a digital object
                    (for example, a chapter title, episode name, or an audio or video clip). </p>
                <p> If a resource has multiple parts, each with its own Part Name, the work should
                    be catalogued in as many records as there are Part Names.
                    <!--NB: not implemented: Multiple Part Name fields may be nested in a single Title Information to describe a single part with multiple hierarchical levels; multiple parts, however, should be separated into multiple Title Information blocks. -->
                </p>
                <p> When representing the Part Name, do not include punctuation at the end of the
                    preceding field intended to separate the part name from previous parts of the
                    title.
                    <!--Multiple parts of an item should appear in separate records or as Related Items.-->
                </p>
            </help>
            <hint/>
            <value>partName</value>
            <local-name>partName</local-name>
            <parent/>
            <tab-id>title</tab-id>
            <tab-id>subject</tab-id>
        </item>
        <item xml:id="hint-code_partNumber">
            <help>
                <p> Part Number is used for a part or section number in a title. </p>
                <p> Use Part Number when a part number is present, rather than including the part
                    number in the text of the Title. </p>
                <p> A Part Number does not have to be a digit, i.e. "First Part" may be the contents
                    of the Part Number field if this is how it occurs on the title page. </p>
                <p> Part Number may describe the section of an digital object (for example, an
                    episode number or an audio or video clip). </p>
                <p> When using Part Number, do not include punctuation at the end of the preceding
                    field intended to separate the part number from previous parts of the title.
                </p>
            </help>
            <hint/>
            <value>partNumber</value>
            <local-name>partNumber</local-name>
            <parent/>
            <tab-id>title</tab-id>
            <tab-id>subject</tab-id>
        </item>
        <item xml:id="hint-code_physicalDescription-compact">
            <help>
                <p> The Extent and (for some types of publication) the Internet Media Type of the
                    publication are noted in Physical Description.</p>
            </help>
            <hint/>
            <value>physicalDescription-compact</value>
            <local-name>physicalDescription</local-name>
            <parent/>
            <tab-id>compact-a</tab-id>
        </item>
        <item xml:id="hint-code_physicalDescription-form">
            <help>
                <p> A designation of a particular physical presentation of a resource. Form includes
                    information that specifies the physical form or medium of material for a
                    resource. Form should be used to characterize the resource itself rather than
                    the content of the resource, which would be Genre. Either a controlled list of
                    values or free text may be used. </p>
            </help>
            <hint/>
            <value>physicalDescription-compact</value>
            <local-name>physicalDescription</local-name>
            <parent/>
            <tab-id>compact-a</tab-id>
            <tab-id>physical-description</tab-id>
        </item>
        <item xml:id="hint-code_physicalDescription-form-type">
            <help>
                <p> This field is used if desired to specify whether the information noted under
                    Form concerns materials or techniques, e.g. type="material": oil paint;
                    type="technique": painting. </p>
            </help>
            <hint/>
            <value>physicalDescription-compact</value>
            <tab-id>physical-description</tab-id>
            <parent/>
            <tab-id>compact-a</tab-id>
        </item>
        <item xml:id="hint-code_physicalDescription-form-authority">
            <help>
                <p> The name of the authoritative list for a controlled value is recorded here. A
                    list of authorities is maintained at:
                    www.loc.gov/marc/sourcecode/form/formsource.html. The MARC 21 form list contains
                    most of the values defined in fields 008/23 (BK, MU, CR, MX) and 008/29 (MP,
                    VM). Use authority="marcform" to indicate its use. </p>
            </help>
            <hint/>
            <value>physicalDescription-compact</value>
            <tab-id>physical-description</tab-id>
            <parent/>
            <tab-id>compact-a</tab-id>
        </item>
        <item xml:id="hint-code_physicalDescription">
            <help>
                <p> Physical Description contains all subfields relating to the physical description
                    information of the resource described. Data is input only within each subfield.
                </p>
            </help>
            <hint/>
            <value>physicalDescription-compact</value>
            <local-name>physicalDescription</local-name>
            <parent/>
            <tab-id>compact-a</tab-id>
            <tab-id>physical-description</tab-id>
        </item>
        <item xml:id="hint-code_physicalLocation">
            <help>
                <p> Record in Physical Location the institution or repository that holds the
                    resource or where it is available. Physical Location may be expressed as text
                    and/or as a code. If expressed as code, use the Authority field to designate the
                    source of the code. </p>
                <p> Physical Location typically includes specific information used to locate a
                    resource within a collection, such as the name or code of an
                    institution/repository, and perhaps sub-collection. A shelf number is given in
                    Shelf Locator. </p>
            </help>
            <hint/>
            <value>physicalLocation</value>
            <local-name>physicalLocation</local-name>
            <parent>location</parent>
            <tab-id>location</tab-id>
        </item>
        <item xml:id="hint-code_place-compact">
            <help>
                <p> Record in City the name of the city in which the publisher has its principal
                    domicile, as noted on the title page. </p>
                <p> If the publisher is housed in several cities, record the one given prominence on
                    the title page. If all are given equal prominence, record the first city
                    name.</p>
                <p> If you have chosen a transliteration scheme when you created the record, you
                    will have the option of entering a transliteration and a translation.</p>
                <p> If the city name is in a language that is usually transliterated, enter the
                    transliterated city name in its field. Use the transliteration scheme you chose
                    when selecting a record template.</p>
            </help>
            <hint/>
            <value>place-compact</value>
            <local-name>place</local-name>
            <parent/>
            <tab-id>compact-a</tab-id>
            <tab-id>compact-b-edited-volume</tab-id>
            <tab-id>compact-b-review</tab-id>
            <tab-id>compact-b-xlink</tab-id>
        </item>
        <item xml:id="hint-code_place">
            <help>
                <p> Record in Place the place names associated with the origin of a resource, i.e.,
                    its creation, publication, issuance, etc.</p>
                <p>Place should be omitted if no information about the originating place of the
                    resource is known.</p>
                <p>Input in Place is performed through Place Terms. If one Place has several Place
                    Terms, e.g. the name of a country and the name of a city, repeat Place Term as
                    necessary, ordering them from higher to lower geographical level.</p>
                <p>If a resource has several places of origin, repeat Place. </p>
            </help>
            <hint/>
            <value>place</value>
            <local-name>place</local-name>
            <parent/>
            <tab-id>origin</tab-id>
        </item>
        <item xml:id="hint-code_placeTerm">
            <help>
                <p> Use Place Term to record the textual or code form of the place.</p>
                <p>If the place is a country, the name of the country can be selected from the MARC
                    country code list or the ISO3166 standard list of country names. If the place is
                    not a country, add Place Term and write the place name (e.g. city name) with
                    Type set to "Text". </p>
            </help>
            <hint/>
            <value>placeTerm</value>
            <local-name>placeTerm</local-name>
            <parent/>
            <tab-id>origin</tab-id>
        </item>
        <item xml:id="hint-code_placeTerm-marccountry">
            <help>
                <p> Names of countries (and US states) according to the marccountry standard list.
                </p>
            </help>
            <hint/>
            <value>placeTerm-marccountry</value>
            <local-name>placeTerm</local-name>
            <parent/>
            <tab-id>titles</tab-id>
        </item>
        <item xml:id="hint-code_placeTerm-text">
            <help>
                <p> Unencoded place terms, i.e. place terms that have not been chosen in an
                    authority file. </p>
            </help>
            <hint/>
            <value>placeTerm-text</value>
            <local-name>placeTerm</local-name>
            <parent/>
            <tab-id>origin</tab-id>
        </item>
        <item xml:id="hint-code_placeTerm-iso3166">
            <help> </help>
            <hint/>
            <value>placeTerm-iso3166</value>
            <local-name>placeTerm</local-name>
            <parent/>
            <tab-id>origin</tab-id>
        </item>
        <item xml:id="hint-code_point">
            <help>
                <p> Use Point if you wish to record a span of time, e.g. 1912-1914.</p>
                <p>The following values are used with Point: start, end.</p>
                <p> Repeat the date field and choose "start" in one and "end" in the other
                    repetition, and enter the appropriate dates in the two date fields. </p>
                <p> If no point is specified, a date is assumed to be a single date, i.e. a whole
                    year, month or day. </p>
            </help>
            <value>point</value>
            <local-name>point</local-name>
            <parent/>
            <tab-id>compact-c</tab-id>
            <tab-id>compact-d</tab-id>
            <tab-id>origin</tab-id>
            <tab-id>subject</tab-id>
            <tab-id>related</tab-id>
            <tab-id>related-xlink</tab-id>
            <tab-id>related-abbreviated</tab-id>
        </item>
        <item xml:id="hint-code_projection">
            <help>
                <p> Projection provides a statement of projection. </p>
            </help>
            <value>projection</value>
            <local-name>projection</local-name>
            <parent>cartographics</parent>
            <tab-id>subject</tab-id>
        </item>
        <item xml:id="hint-code_province">
            <help>
                <p> Includes first order political divisions called provinces within a country, e.g.
                    Canada. </p>
            </help>
            <value>province</value>
            <local-name>province</local-name>
            <parent>hierarchicalGeographic</parent>
            <tab-id>subject</tab-id>
        </item>
        <item xml:id="hint-code_publisher-compact">
            <help>
                <p> Record in Publisher the name of the entity that is the originator for a
                    resource, i.e. that has published, printed, distributed, released, issued, or
                    produced it, as noted on the title page. </p>
                <p> If you have chosen a transliteration scheme when you created the record, you
                    will have the option of entering a transliteration and a translation.</p>
                <p> If the publisher name is in a language that is usually transliterated, enter the
                    transliterated publisher name in its field. Use the transliteration scheme you
                    chose when selecting a record template. </p>
            </help>
            <hint/>
            <value>publisher-compact</value>
            <local-name>publisher</local-name>
            <parent/>
            <tab-id>compact-a</tab-id>
            <tab-id>compact-b-edited-volume</tab-id>
            <tab-id>compact-b-review</tab-id>
            <tab-id>compact-b-xlink</tab-id>
        </item>
        <item xml:id="hint-code_publisher">
            <help>
                <p> Record in Publisher the name of the entity that is the originator for a
                    resource, i.e. that has published, printed, distributed, released, issued, or
                    produced it, as noted on the title page. </p>
                <p> If you have chosen a transliteration scheme when you created the record, you
                    will have the option of entering a transliteration and a translation.</p>
                <p> If the publisher name is in a language that is usually transliterated, enter the
                    transliterated publisher name in its field. Use the transliteration scheme you
                    chose when selecting a record template. </p>
            </help>
            <hint/>
            <value>publisher</value>
            <local-name>publisher</local-name>
            <parent/>
            <tab-id>origin</tab-id>
        </item>
        <item xml:id="hint-code_qualifier">
            <help>
                <p> When a date is uncertain or supplied by the cataloger, indicate this through the
                    use of Qualifier rather than inserting characters such as "ca.", brackets, or a
                    question mark as part of the date string. When only a decade is known, enter a
                    date range for the entire decade and mark the date as questionable. When only a
                    century is known, enter a date range for the entire century and mark the date as
                    questionable. </p>
            </help>
            <value>qualifier</value>
            <local-name>qualifier</local-name>
            <parent/>
            <tab-id>origin</tab-id>
            <tab-id>subject</tab-id>
            <tab-id>related</tab-id>
            <tab-id>related-xlink</tab-id>
            <tab-id>related-abbreviated</tab-id>
        </item>
        <item xml:id="hint-code_region">
            <help>
                <p> Includes regions that have status as a jurisdiction, usually incorporating more
                    than one first level jurisdiction. </p>
            </help>
            <value>region</value>
            <local-name>region</local-name>
            <parent>hierarchicalGeographic</parent>
            <tab-id>subject</tab-id>
        </item>
        <item xml:id="hint-code_relatedItem-periodical-compact">
            <help>
                <p> Enter here information related to the periodical that the article you are
                    cataloguing occurs in. </p>
                <p> This information falls into two groups: general information relating to the
                    periodical and specific information relating to the location of the article in
                    the periodical.</p>
            </help>
            <value>relatedItem-periodical-compact</value>
            <local-name>relatedItem</local-name>
            <parent/>
            <tab-id>compact-b-article</tab-id>
            <tab-id>compact-b-newspaper-article</tab-id>
        </item>
        <item xml:id="hint-code_relatedItem-periodical-titleInfo-compact">
            <help>
                <p> Enter here the title of the periodical you are cataloguing. If the title divides
                    into a main title and a subtitle, enter each part in its separate field. </p>
                <p> If you have chosen a transliteration scheme when you created the record, you
                    will have the option of entering a transliteration and a translation.</p>
                <p> If the title is in a language that is usually transliterated, enter the
                    transliterated title and subtitle in their respective fields. Use the
                    transliteration scheme you chose when selecting a record template. </p>
                <p> If you believe it is useful to supply a translation of the title, do so in the
                    relevant fields. If the language that the title information is translated into
                    is not English, you should choose another language. </p>
            </help>
            <value>relatedItem-periodical-titleInfo-compact</value>
            <local-name>relatedItem</local-name>
            <parent/>
            <tab-id>compact-b-article</tab-id>
            <tab-id>compact-b-newspaper-article</tab-id>
        </item>
        <item xml:id="hint-code_other-location">
            <help>
                <p> Record here the location of the article, book review or contribution inside its
                    host publication, that is, inside its periodical or edited volume.</p>
                <p>If the publication has several parts inside the same host, repeat the block.</p>
                <p>The host publication, that is, the publication that the article, book review or
                    contribution is included in, is shown above. It was on the detail view of this
                    publication that the present record was created. Clicking on the link will take
                    you to the record in question.</p>
            </help>
            <hint/>
            <value>other-location</value>
            <local-name>relatedItem</local-name>
            <parent/>
            <tab-id>compact-b-xlink</tab-id>
        </item>
        <item xml:id="hint-code_book-review">
            <help>
                <p>Record here information regarding where the book review itself has been
                    published. This is the same as cataloguing an article in a periodical. </p>
                <p>Record the title of the book review itself, regardless of whether or not it
                    contains part of or all of the title, etc. of the book being reviewed. </p>
                <p>This information falls into two parts: general information relating to the
                    periodical and information relating to the specific location of the review in
                    the periodical.</p>
            </help>
            <hint/>
            <value>book-review</value>
            <local-name>relatedItem</local-name>
            <parent/>
            <tab-id>compact-b-review</tab-id>
        </item>
        <item xml:id="hint-code_book-reviewed">
            <help>
                <p>Record here information regarding the book reviewed in the book review. This is
                    the same as cataloguing a book. </p>
                <p> Record the title of the book review itself, regardless of whether or not it
                    contains part of or all of the title, etc. of the book being reviewed. </p>
                <p>This information falls into two parts: general information relating to the
                    periodical and information relating to the specific location of the review in
                    the periodical.</p>
            </help>
            <hint/>
            <value>book-reviewed</value>
            <local-name>relatedItem</local-name>
            <parent/>
            <tab-id>compact-b-review</tab-id>
            <tab-id>compact-b-xlink</tab-id>
        </item>
        <item xml:id="hint-code_edited-volume-compact">
            <help>
                <p> Enter here information related to the edited volume that the contribution you
                    are cataloguing occurs in. </p>
                <p>This information falls into two groups: <ul>
                        <li>general information on the edited volume</li>
                        <li>specific information on the location of the contribution in the edited
                            volume</li>
                    </ul>
                </p>
                <p>There are two ways you can supply this information: <ul>
                        <li>you can fill out the title, editors, etc. of the edited volume</li>
                        <li>you can supply the ID number of the edited volume and then fill out the
                            information on the location of the contribution in the edited
                            volume</li>
                    </ul>
                </p>
                <p>If you are cataloguing several contributions from the same edited volume, it is a
                    good idea first to catalogue the edited volume. This will save you time and
                    produce a more ordered bibliography. When you have finished with cataloguing the
                    edited volume, you can then choose "Create Related Record" in the detail view
                    for the record in question. The ID number for the edited volume will then
                    automatically be inserted and you only have to fill out the information
                    particular to the contribution itself. If you are only cataloguing one
                    contribution, you can also follow this way - others may then use your record (if
                    you make it available to them) and catalogue other contributions in the same
                    edited volume, by finding it and clicking "Create Related MODS Record". </p>
                <p> If you choose to enter the information concerning the edited volume inside the
                    record for the contribution, that is, not to use XLink, this is also fine. If
                    you later decide to use the ID of the record for the edited volume, you may
                    insert its ID in the XLink field. </p>
            </help>
            <value>edited-volume-compact</value>
            <local-name>relatedItem</local-name>
            <parent>mods</parent>
            <tab-id>compact-b-edited-volume</tab-id>
        </item>
        <item xml:id="hint-code_series-compact">
            <help>
                <p> Enter here information related to the monograph series that the book you are
                    cataloguing occurs in. </p>
                <p> This information falls into two groups: <ul>
                        <li>general information on the monograph series </li>
                        <li>specific information on the place (number) of the book within the
                            monograph series</li>
                    </ul>
                </p>
                <p> There are two ways you can supply this information: <ul>
                        <li>you can fill out the title, editors, etc. of the monograph series on
                            this form</li>
                        <li>you can supply the ID number of a record cataloguing the monograph
                            series and then fill out the information on the place (number) of the
                            book within the monograph series</li>
                    </ul>
                </p>
                <p> In connection with monograph series, the first approach is the most common.</p>
                <p> If you enter the information concerning the monograph series inside the record
                    for the book, that is, not to use the ID of the series, you can later decide to
                    use the ID of the record for the monograph series, by inserting its ID in the
                    XLink field and removing the information you have supplied about the title of
                    the monograph series. </p>
                <p> If you are cataloguing several books from the same series, it is a good idea
                    first to catalogue the series. This will save you time and produce a more
                    ordered bibliography. When you have finished with cataloguing the series, you
                    can choose "Create Related MODS Record" in the detail view for the record in
                    question. The ID number for the series will then automatically be inserted and
                    you only have to fill out the information particular to the book itself (its
                    place within the series and so on). If you are only cataloguing one book, you
                    can also follow this way - others may then use your record (if you make it
                    available to them) and catalogue other books in the same series, by finding it
                    and likewise clicking "Create Related MODS Record". </p>
            </help>
            <value>series-compact</value>
            <local-name>relatedItem</local-name>
            <parent>mods</parent>
            <tab-id>compact-b-monograph</tab-id>
        </item>
        <item xml:id="hint-code_series-edited-volume-compact">
            <help>
                <p> Enter here information related to the monograph series that the edited volume
                    you are cataloguing occurs in. </p>
                <p>This information falls into two groups: general information on the monograph
                    series and specific information on the location of the edited volume in the
                    monograph series.</p>
                <p>In order not to make matter more complicated than necessary, only information
                    relating to the title of the series and the location of the edited volume within
                    the series is included.</p>
                <p> Please note that the information concerning Monograph Series of Edited Volume is
                    not displayed.</p>
                <p>The option to input an XLink for the series is similar to that for the edited
                    volume itself.</p>
            </help>
            <value>series-edited-volume-compact</value>
            <local-name>relatedItem</local-name>
            <parent>relatedItem</parent>
            <tab-id>compact-b-edited-volume</tab-id>
        </item>
        <item xml:id="hint-code_role-compact">
            <help>
                <p> Role contains a description of the role of the person or institution named above
                    to the resource being catalogued.</p>
                <p> Repeat Role for each new role played by the named entity, i.e. the same person
                    or institution can have several roles in relation to one resource.</p>
            </help>
            <hint/>
            <value>role-compact</value>
            <local-name>role</local-name>
            <parent>name</parent>
            <tab-id>compact-a</tab-id>
            <tab-id>compact-b-review</tab-id>
            <tab-id>compact-b-xlink</tab-id>
        </item>
        <item xml:id="hint-code_role">
            <help>
                <p>Role contains a coded and/or textual description of the role of the person,
                    corporation or conference entered into Name Part to the resource being
                    catalogued. Repeat Role for each new role played by the person, corporation or
                    conference.</p>
            </help>
            <hint/>
            <value>role</value>
            <local-name>role</local-name>
            <parent>name</parent>
            <tab-id>name</tab-id>
            <tab-id>mads</tab-id>
        </item>
        <item xml:id="hint-code_roleTerm">
            <help>
                <p>Role contains a coded and/or textual description of the role of the person,
                    corporation or conference entered into Name Part to the resource being
                    catalogued. An authority should be indicated if using a coded form for role. </p>
                <p> Coded input is preselected as Type. The MARC Code List for Relators is
                    preselected as Authority, with the most common roles placed at the top. </p>
                <p> If both a coded term and a textual term are given that represent the same role,
                    use one Role and two occurrences of Role Term.</p>
            </help>
            <hint/>
            <value>roleTerm</value>
            <local-name>roleTerm</local-name>
            <parent>role</parent>
            <tab-id>name</tab-id>
            <tab-id>mads</tab-id>
        </item>
        <item xml:id="hint-code_roleTerm-code">
            <help>
                <p>Select a Role Term from the list. </p>
                <p> Note that "Author" is primarily used in connection with printed resources,
                    whereas "Creator" is primarily used in connection with other resources.</p>
            </help>
            <hint/>
            <value>roleTerm-code</value>
            <local-name>roleTerm</local-name>
            <parent>role</parent>
            <tab-id>name</tab-id>
            <tab-id>mads</tab-id>
        </item>
        <item xml:id="hint-code_roleTerm-text">
            <help>
                <p>Select a term from the list. </p>
                <p> The list of terms given if "Text" is chosen for Type is the same as the list
                    given if "Code" is chosen for Type and Authority is MARC Code List for Relators.
                    However, the values entered into the database are different. If Code is chosen,
                    "aut" will e.g. be input, whereas "Author" will be input if "Text" is chosen. It
                    is recommended to input each role in both coded and textual form. </p>
                <p> If "Text" is chosen, you can also input a term not on the list.</p>
            </help>
            <hint/>
            <value>roleTerm-text</value>
            <local-name>roleTerm</local-name>
            <parent>role</parent>
            <tab-id>name</tab-id>
            <tab-id>mads</tab-id>
        </item>
        <item xml:id="hint-code_roleTerm-type">
            <help>
                <p>Type is used to express whether the Role Term has textual or coded form.</p>
            </help>
            <hint/>
            <value>roleTerm-type</value>
            <local-name>roleTerm</local-name>
            <parent>role</parent>
            <tab-id>name</tab-id>
            <tab-id>mads</tab-id>
        </item>
        <item xml:id="hint-code_roleTerm-authority">
            <help>
                <p>If the Type is in coded form, the authority file followed must be indicated.</p>
            </help>
            <hint/>
            <value>roleTerm-authority</value>
            <local-name>roleTerm</local-name>
            <parent>role</parent>
            <tab-id>name</tab-id>
            <tab-id>mads</tab-id>
        </item>
        <item xml:id="hint-code_scale">
            <help>
                <p> Scale provides a statement of scale. It may include any equivalency statements,
                    vertical scales or vertical exaggeration statements for relief models and other
                    three-dimensional items. </p>
            </help>
            <value>scale</value>
            <local-name>scale</local-name>
            <parent>cartographics</parent>
            <tab-id>subject</tab-id>
        </item>
        <item xml:id="hint-code_name-script">
            <help>
                <p> Use Script to record the script in which the name in rendered. </p>
                <p>Script can be applied the Name as a whole. Do this if you are using only one
                    Script value for all Name Parts. If you are using different values for different
                    Name Parts, apply Script to each Name Part and leave Script empty under Name as
                    a whole. </p>
            </help>
            <hint/>
            <value>name-script</value>
            <local-name>script</local-name>
            <parent/>
            <tab-id>name</tab-id>
            <tab-id>identifier</tab-id>
            <tab-id>mads</tab-id>
        </item>
        <item xml:id="hint-code_namePart-script">
            <help>
                <p>Use Script to record the script in which the name in rendered. </p>
                <p> Script can be applied the Name as a whole. Do this if you are using only one
                    Script value for all Name Parts. If you are using different values for different
                    Name Parts, apply Script to each Name Part and leave Script empty under Name as
                    a whole.</p>
            </help>
            <hint/>
            <value>namePart-script</value>
            <local-name>script</local-name>
            <parent/>
            <tab-id>name</tab-id>
            <tab-id>mads</tab-id>
        </item>
        <item xml:id="hint-code_originInfo-script">
            <help>
                <p> If the Origin Information is in a non-Latin script, note here the script
                    utilised. As transliterations use the Latin script, the Transliteration field
                    becomes unnecessary when Latin script is chosen. </p>
                <p> Script can be applied the Origin Information as a whole. Do this if you are
                    using only one Script value for all Place Terms, for Publisher and for Edition.
                    If you are using different Script values inside Origin Information, apply Script
                    to each field and leave Script empty under Origin Information. </p>
            </help>
            <hint/>
            <value>originInfo-script</value>
            <local-name>script</local-name>
            <parent/>
            <tab-id>origin</tab-id>
        </item>
        <item xml:id="hint-code_script">
            <help>
                <p> Script specifies the script used within individual fields. The use of Latin
                    script is not noted. </p>
                <p>"Chinese" is "Han (Simplified Variant)" or "Han (Traditional Variant)". If the
                    two variants are not considered, it is "Han (Hanzi, Kanji, Hanja)", which is
                    also used for Japanese, Korean and Vietnamese written in Chinese. </p>
            </help>
            <hint/>
            <value>script</value>
            <local-name>script</local-name>
            <parent/>
            <tab-id>name</tab-id>
            <tab-id>title</tab-id>
            <tab-id>part</tab-id>
            <tab-id>related</tab-id>
            <tab-id>related-abbreviated</tab-id>
            <tab-id>related-xlink</tab-id>
            <tab-id>physical-description</tab-id>
            <tab-id>access-condition</tab-id>
            <tab-id>language</tab-id>
            <tab-id>genre</tab-id>
            <tab-id>location</tab-id>
            <tab-id>mads</tab-id>
            <tab-id>note</tab-id>
            <tab-id>subject</tab-id>
            <tab-id>abstract</tab-id>
            <tab-id>table-of-contents</tab-id>
            <tab-id>target-audience</tab-id>
            <tab-id>classification</tab-id>
            <tab-id>record-info</tab-id>
        </item>
        <item xml:id="hint-code_script-global-compact">
            <help>
                <p> Script specifies the script used within individual fields. The use of Latin
                    script is not noted. "Chinese" is "Han (Simplified Variant)" or "Han
                    (Traditional Variant)". If the two variants are not considered, it is "Han
                    (Hanzi, Kanji, Hanja)", which is also used for Japanese, Korean and Vietnamese
                    written in Chinese. </p>
                <p>The script noted here is the script chosen when the record was created. It
                    applies to the record as a whole, unless otherwise noted. Since a title or a
                    name as a subject can be in any script, the Global Script can be overruled here
                    by choosing a Local Script.</p>
            </help>
            <hint/>
            <value>script-global-compact</value>
            <local-name>script</local-name>
            <parent/>
            <tab-id>titles</tab-id>
        </item>
        <item xml:id="hint-code_script-local-compact">
            <help>
                <p> Script specifies the script used within individual fields. The use of Latin
                    script is not noted. "Chinese" is "Han (Simplified Variant)" or "Han
                    (Traditional Variant)". If the two variants are not considered, it is "Han
                    (Hanzi, Kanji, Hanja)", which is also used for Japanese, Korean and Vietnamese
                    written in Chinese. </p>
                <p>The script noted here is not the script chosen when the record was created. the
                    script noted here only applies to the field(s) immediately below. Since a title
                    or a name as a subject can be in any script, the Global Script can be overruled
                    here by choosing a Local Script.</p>
            </help>
            <hint/>
            <value>script-local-compact</value>
            <local-name>script</local-name>
            <parent/>
            <tab-id>compact-d</tab-id>
        </item>
        <item xml:id="hint-code_script-compact">
            <help>
                <p> Global Script specifies the script used within individual fields. The use of
                    Latin script is not noted.</p>
                <p> "Chinese" is "Han (Simplified Variant)" or "Han (Traditional Variant)". If the
                    two variants are not considered, it is "Han (Hanzi, Kanji, Hanja)", also used
                    for Japanese, Korean and Vietnamese written in Chinese. </p>
                <p> Note that the value shown here is the value selected when a record template was
                    chosen. This value applies to the whole record, not just to the field above
                    which it is noted. If you change the value, the change will apply to the whole
                    record. </p>
                <p>If you need to specify a script for an individual field that is different from
                    the global script, you should use the Citation Forms. Here script can be applied
                    to individual fields.</p>
            </help>
            <hint/>
            <value>script-compact</value>
            <local-name>script</local-name>
            <parent/>
            <tab-id>compact-a</tab-id>
        </item>
        <item xml:id="hint-code_scriptTerm">
            <help>
                <p>Script Term may be expressed in textual or coded form.</p>
                <p>If in coded form, the source of the code is contained in the value of the
                    authority attribute. If no authority is given, it is assumed that the content is
                    textual.</p>
                <p>If there is more than one representation of the same script (e.g., text and
                    code), Script Term is repeated. If the record is in more than one script,
                    Language Of Cataloging is repeated.</p>
            </help>
            <hint/>
            <value>scriptTerm</value>
            <local-name>scriptTerm</local-name>
            <parent>language</parent>
            <tab-id>language</tab-id>
            <tab-id>record-info</tab-id>
        </item>
        <item xml:id="hint-code_shelfLocator">
            <help>
                <p> Shelf Locator records a shelf-mark or other shelving designation that indicates
                    the location identifier for a copy. If more detailed holdings information is
                    given at the item level, use Shelf Locator under Holding Simple. </p>
            </help>
            <hint/>
            <value>shelfLocator</value>
            <local-name>shelfLocator</local-name>
            <parent>location</parent>
            <tab-id>location</tab-id>
        </item>
        <item xml:id="hint-code_state">
            <help>
                <p> Includes first order political divisions called states within a country, e.g. in
                    U.S., Argentina, Italy. Use also for France département. </p>
            </help>
            <value>state</value>
            <local-name>state</local-name>
            <parent>hierarchicalGeographic</parent>
            <tab-id>subject</tab-id>
        </item>
        <item xml:id="hint-code_subject">
            <help>
                <p> A Subject is a term or a phrase that represents the primary topic(s) on which a
                    work is focused. Use at least one Subject field in each record to allow
                    retrieval of the record by its contents. Enter as many specific terms as
                    necessary to capture the contents. Be consistent in the formatting of Subject
                    terms. </p>
                <p> A publication is often on a number of different subjects. If these are separate
                    subjects, repeat the Subject instead of storing diverse information inside one
                    Subject.</p>
                <p> Values for Subject indicate which contents is found within or represented by the
                    work, and these values typically answer such questions as who, what, where, and
                    when.</p>
                <p> While it is allowed to place multiple values in a single Subject field, such as
                    within on Topic field, it is the preferred practice to split up Subject terms
                    into separate sub-fields, each of which answer the question of who, what, where,
                    and when in relation to the resource being catalogued. Analyse as much as
                    possible.</p>
                <p> A Subject is basically composed of a Topic, a Place reference and a Time
                    reference. All these fields are optional, that is, one can have a Topic without
                    any Place or Time reference, and one can have a Place reference without a Topic
                    or a Time reference. To have a Time reference all on its own would be a little
                    unusual, but if period labels are used, this might still be acceptable.</p>
                <p> Topics can be divided into different kinds: "plain" Topics, Name topics and Work
                    topics. "Plain" topics are references to abstract or concrete entities that are
                    not persons or organisations or works created by these. Topics of this kind are
                    "beauty" or "bicycle", "democracy" or "doors". No distinction is made between
                    abstract or concrete topics. </p>
                <p> In addition to plain topics, a person or an institution can serve as topic,
                    examples being "George Washington" or "United Nations." These are identified by
                    their names. If a work of literature or art, or any other creation, serves as
                    topic, it is identified by its title. These three subtypes address different
                    aspects of the "what" of a subject. </p>
                <p> In order not to complicate matters, no notice is here taken of language, script,
                    transliteration, etc. If you need to enter information using these categories,
                    select the Subjects tab on Content Description Forms.</p>
                <p> The "where" of a subject can be expressed in a number of ways. "Place" simply
                    contains the name of the place. </p>
                <p> "Time", the answer to "when," can be encoded in a number of different ways. The
                    recommendation is to use the w3cdtf encoding. According to this encoding, dates
                    are formatted in the following way: Year: YYYY (e.g. 1997); Year and month:
                    YYYY-MM (e.g. 1997-07); Complete date: YYYY-MM-DD (e.g. 1997-07-16). </p>
                <p> Date ranges are indicated using "start" and "end" in Point. If a date range is
                    open to one side, leave that side blank. If the date is completely unknown,
                    leave the Date field blank. </p>
                <p> In Time one can also use period designations, such as "the Middle Ages" and
                    "Industrialisation," with the dangers of differing construals of what these
                    labels denote. If you enter a time designation which uses a designation of this
                    type, choose "text" in type.</p>
                <p> More input options can be accessed by clicking the Subjects tab on Content
                    Description Forms.</p>
            </help>
            <hint/>
            <value>subject</value>
            <local-name>subject</local-name>
            <parent/>
            <tab-id>compact-c</tab-id>
            <tab-id>compact-d</tab-id>
            <tab-id>subject</tab-id>
        </item>
        <item xml:id="hint-code_subTitle">
            <help>
                <p> Subtitle is used to record a part of a title that is secondary to the core
                    title. </p>
                <p> Use Subtitle whenever a subtitle is present, rather than including the subtitle
                    in Title. </p>
                <p> When using Subtitle, do not include punctuation intended to separate the title
                    from the subtitle at the end of Title. </p>
                <p> If more than two levels are in evidence in the whole title, i.e. if there is a
                    sub-subtitle, include the sub-subtitle in Subtitle, with appropriate
                    punctuation. <!--NB: What are the rules here? Should not subTitle repeat?-->
                </p>
                <p> Subtitle contains every part of the title that do not belong in Non Sort, Title,
                    Part Number or Part Name. </p>
            </help>
            <hint/>
            <value>subTitle</value>
            <local-name>subTitle</local-name>
            <parent/>
            <tab-id>title</tab-id>
            <tab-id>subject</tab-id>
        </item>
        <item xml:id="hint-code_subTitle-compact">
            <help>
                <p> Subtitle is used to record a part of a title that is secondary to the core
                    title. </p>
                <p> Use Subtitle whenever a subtitle is present, rather than including the subtitle
                    in Title. </p>
                <p> Subtitle contains every part of the title that do not belong in Non Sort, Title,
                    Part Number or Part Name. </p>
            </help>
            <hint/>
            <value>subTitle-compact</value>
            <local-name>subTitle</local-name>
            <parent/>
            <tab-id>compact-a</tab-id>
            <tab-id>compact-b-article</tab-id>
            <tab-id>compact-b-newspaper-article</tab-id>
            <tab-id>compact-b-review</tab-id>
            <tab-id>compact-b-xlink</tab-id>
        </item>
        <item xml:id="hint-code_supplied">
            <help>
                <p>Supplied indicates that the information does not come from the resource itself,
                    but has been supplied by the cataloguer.</p>
            </help>
            <hint/>
            <value>supplied</value>
            <local-name>supplied</local-name>
            <parent>originInfo</parent>
            <parent>titleInfo</parent>
            <tab-id>subject</tab-id>
            <tab-id>origin</tab-id>
            <tab-id>compact-b-moving-images</tab-id>
        </item>
        <item xml:id="hint-code_digitalOrigin">
            <help>
                <p> A designation of the source of a digital file important to its creation, use and
                    management. Digital Origin may indicate the source of a digital file important
                    to its creation, use and management. </p>
            </help>
            <hint/>
            <value>supplied</value>
            <local-name>supplied</local-name>
            <parent>originInfo</parent>
            <parent>titleInfo</parent>
            <tab-id>origin</tab-id>
        </item>
        <item xml:id="hint-code_targetAudience">
            <help>
                <p> Use Target Audience to describe a group for which a resource is intended. </p>
                <p> Use this field whenever there is a specific audience for a resource (for
                    example, a text marked up specifically for historians). Do not limit the use of
                    Target Audience to the intellectual level of the audience (as suggested by the
                    marctarget list). </p>
                <p> If you wish to add an authority file, or wish to add terms to the Local
                    authority file, please contact <!--contact-->. When more than one target
                    audience is recorded, the field is repeated. </p>
                <p> Use the authority field whenever possible to indicate the controlled vocabulary
                    used. </p>
                <p> Do not use Target Audience to indicate audiences to whom access or use of the
                    resource is limited; include this information in the Access Condition field.
                </p>
            </help>
            <hint/>
            <value>targetAudience</value>
            <local-name>targetAudience</local-name>
            <parent/>
            <tab-id>target-audience</tab-id>
        </item>
        <item xml:id="hint-code_template">
            <help>
                <p>Choose one of the publication types listed below. These publication types are the
                    same as the record templates used in the pre-entry options. </p>
                <p> If a record has not been made by use of Tamboti, you can assign a publication
                    type to it here.</p>
                <p> If you have assigned a wrong publication type in the pre-entry dialogue, you can
                    change it here. Changing it here will however not change the options displayed
                    in the Basic Input Forms until you save the record and reopen it.</p>
            </help>
            <hint/>
            <value>template</value>
            <local-name>template</local-name>
            <parent>extension</parent>
            <tab-id>extension</tab-id>
        </item>
        <item xml:id="hint-code_temporal">
            <help>
                <p> Use Time for chronological Subject terms to denote temporal coverage. Time may
                    be expressed as a term (e.g. "Middle Ages") or as a structured date (e.g.
                    "2001-09-11"). In the first case, choose "text" in Type; otherwise choose
                    "YYY-MM-DD" and enter the time you wish to refer to as precisely as
                    possible.</p>
                <p> One may leave out the MM and DD parts, to denote larger stretches of time. For
                    more options, use the Extended Date-Time Format
                    (http://www.loc.gov/standards/datetime/).</p>
                <p> Point is used to note whether the date noted is a start point or an end point
                    when using a structured date. If no point is specified, date is assumed to be a
                    single date. </p>
                <p> More input options can be accessed by clicking the Subjects tab on Content
                    Description Forms.</p>
            </help>
            <hint/>
            <value>temporal</value>
            <local-name>temporal</local-name>
            <parent/>
            <tab-id>compact-c</tab-id>
            <tab-id>compact-d</tab-id>
            <tab-id>subject</tab-id>
        </item>
        <item xml:id="hint-code_territory">
            <help>
                <p> Name of a geographical area belonging to or under the jurisdiction of a
                    governmental authority. </p>
            </help>
            <value>territory</value>
            <local-name>territory</local-name>
            <parent>hierarchicalGeographic</parent>
            <tab-id>subject</tab-id>
        </item>
        <item xml:id="hint-code_title">
            <help>
                <p> Title contains the core title of the resource catalogued. </p>
                <p> At least one Title is required. When no title appears on the item being
                    described, a title should be supplied. </p>
                <p> Title includes all parts of a title that are not covered by Non Sort, Subtitle,
                    Part Number and Part Name. </p>
                <p> Dates may be recorded under Title or Subtitle only if they are part of the
                    title. Publication dates are included under Origin Information. </p>
                <p> For parallel titles, i.e., equivalent titles in different languages that have
                    not been translated by the cataloguer, add a Title Information and enter the
                    Title there with the Type "Alternative" for each parallel title. Note the
                    language, script and transliteration of each title. </p>
                <p> For a title translated or transcribed by the cataloguer, add a Title Information
                    and enter the Title there with the Type "Translated" or "Transliterated" for
                    each title. Note the language, script and transliteration of each title added in
                    this way. </p>
                <p> For abbreviated titles, add a Title Information block and enter the Title there
                    with the Type "Abbreviated" for each parallel title. </p>
                <p> For uniform titles, i.e., titles with various renderings that are unified by an
                    authority file, add a Title Information and enter the Title there with the Type
                    "Uniform". Under each uniform title, state the Authority according to which the
                    uniform title has been selected. </p>
            </help>
            <hint/>
            <value>title</value>
            <local-name>title</local-name>
            <parent/>
            <tab-id>title</tab-id>
            <tab-id>subject</tab-id>
        </item>
        <item xml:id="hint-code_title-compact">
            <help>
                <p> Title contains the core title of the resource catalogued. </p>
                <p> At least one Title is required. When no title appears on the item being
                    described, a title should be supplied. </p>
                <p> Title includes all parts of a title that are not covered by Non Sort, Subtitle,
                    Part Number and Part Name. </p>
            </help>
            <hint/>
            <value>title-compact</value>
            <local-name>title</local-name>
            <parent/>
            <tab-id>compact-a</tab-id>
            <tab-id>compact-b-article</tab-id>
            <tab-id>compact-b-newspaper-article</tab-id>
            <tab-id>compact-b-review</tab-id>
            <tab-id>compact-b-xlink</tab-id>
        </item>
        <item xml:id="hint-code_subject-titleInfo">
            <help>
                <p> Title Information is used under Subject to note when the resource catalogued is
                    about another resource with a title, e.g. when it is a book about another book
                    or an article about a work of art. The aim is here not to refer to a concrete
                    publication, but to a more abstract work. This may be a written work, such as
                    "Hamlet", a work of art, such a "Guernica", or a work of music, such as "The
                    Wall", etc.</p>
                <p> (Note that there is no regular way of recording authorship, editorship and so
                    on. If a person or institution needs to be pointed to in order to identify a
                    work, one can add such a reference in Persons and Institutions as Topic, but
                    there is no place to specify the relation of the person or institution to the
                    work.).</p>
                <p> If the title divides into a main title and a subtitle, enter each part in its
                    separate field. </p>
                <p> A Title Information consists of a Title and fields that relate to it. A Title
                    may have a Subtitle, usually an expansion of the Title proper. If the Title
                    begins with a word according to which it should not be sorted (such as "The" or
                    "A" and the like), enter this word in Non Sort and remove it from Title. </p>
                <p> The division between basic, alternative, translated, transliterated or uniform
                    titles is not observed here, in the interest of simplicity. If you need to enter
                    information using these categories, select the Subjects tab on Content
                    Description Forms.</p>
                <p> Part Number and Part Name are not used here. If you need to enter information
                    using these categories, select the Subjects tab on Content Description Forms. </p>
                <p> The language, script and transliteration of the title is not recorded in this
                    interface. If you need to enter information using these categories, select the
                    Subjects tab on Content Description Forms. </p>
                <p> More input options can be accessed by clicking the Subjects tab on Content
                    Description Forms.</p>
            </help>
            <hint/>
            <value>subject-titleInfo</value>
            <local-name>titleInfo</local-name>
            <parent/>
            <tab-id>compact-c</tab-id>
            <tab-id>compact-d</tab-id>
            <tab-id>subject</tab-id>
        </item>
        <item xml:id="hint-code_titleInfo">
            <help>
                <p> At least one Title inside a Title Information is required. Title Information can
                    be repeated for alternative, translated, transliterated or uniform titles. These
                    values are chosen in Type. For the basic Title Information entry, leave Type
                    blank or use the value "Basic Title Information". If, in addition to the basic
                    title, you also wish to record an alternative, translated, transliterated or
                    uniform title, add a Title Information and choose the relevant Type. Repeat
                    Title Information as many times as necessary. </p>
                <p> A Title Information consists of a main Title, plus a number of supplementary
                    fields that relate to it. A Title may have a Subtitle, usually an expansion of
                    the Title proper. If the Title begins with a word according to which it should
                    not be sorted (such as "The" or "A" and the like), enter this word in Non Sort
                    and remove it from Title. If a publication consists of several parts, parts that
                    are either numbered or named, use Part Number and/or Part Name. "A History of
                    Philosophy" may have several numbered parts, such as "Part One. Ancient Greek
                    Philosophy." Enter "Part One" in Part Number and "Ancient Greek Philosophy" in
                    Part Name. </p>
                <p> When no title appears on the item being described, a title should be supplied.
                    Use Display Label to indicate that the title is supplied, by giving it the value
                    "Supplied Title". A supplied title should be created in accordance with an
                    established standard and describe, as concisely as possible, the content of the
                    resource in question. If no standards apply, consider carefully the expectations
                    users have for the naming of similar resources. </p>
                <p> If an alternative, translated or transliterated title is recorded, choose the
                    relevant Type for each separate Title Information. </p>
                <p> If a uniform or an abbreviated title is recorded, choose the appropriate value
                    in Type and note in which authority file the uniform or abbreviated title in
                    Authority has been found. Authority files are only used in connection with
                    uniform and abbreviated titles. </p>
                <p> Record the language of the Title Information by choosing the language used in
                    the resource, if this is different from the language noted in Language of
                    Resource, a field describing the language of the resource as a whole. The
                    Language of Resource was selected when opening the editor; it may be modified in
                    the Resource Languages tab.</p>
            </help>
            <hint/>
            <value>titleInfo</value>
            <local-name>titleInfo</local-name>
            <parent/>
            <tab-id>title</tab-id>
        </item>
        <item xml:id="hint-code_titleInfo-compact">
            <help>
                <p> Enter here the title of the publication that you are cataloguing. This
                    publication may be a book, an edited volume, a periodical, an article, or a
                    contribution to an edited volume.</p>
                <p> If the title divides into a main title and a subtitle, enter each part in its
                    separate field. If the subtitle divides into several parts, separate the parts
                    with a semicolon. </p>
                <p> Non Sort contains characters, including initial articles (typically "A" and
                    "The" in English) that appear at the beginning of a title that should be ignored
                    when sorting. </p>
                <p> If you have chosen a transliteration scheme when you created the record, you
                    will have the option of entering a transliteration and a translation.</p>
                <p> If the title is in a language that is usually transliterated, enter the
                    transliterated title and subtitle in their respective fields. Use the
                    transliteration scheme you chose when selecting a record template.</p>
                <p> If you believe it is useful to supply a translation of the title, do so in the
                    relevant fields. If the language that the title information is translated into
                    is not English, you should choose another language. </p>
            </help>
            <hint/>
            <value>titleInfo-compact</value>
            <local-name>titleInfo</local-name>
            <parent/>
            <tab-id>compact-a</tab-id>
            <tab-id>compact-b-review</tab-id>
            <tab-id>compact-b-xlink</tab-id>
        </item>
        <item xml:id="hint-code_edited-volume-titleInfo-compact">
            <help>
                <p> Enter here the title of the edited volume you are cataloguing. If the title
                    divides into a main title and a subtitle, enter each part in its separate field. </p>
                <p> If you have chosen a transliteration scheme when you created the record, you
                    will have the option of entering a transliteration and a translation.</p>
                <p> If the title is in a language that is usually transliterated, enter the
                    transliterated title and subtitle in their respective fields. Use the
                    transliteration scheme you chose when selecting a record template. </p>
                <p> If you believe it is useful to supply a translation of the title, do so in the
                    relevant fields. If the language that the title information is translated into
                    is not English, you should choose another language. </p>
            </help>
            <value>edited-volume-titleInfo-compact</value>
            <local-name>titleInfo</local-name>
            <parent/>
            <tab-id>compact-b-edited-volume</tab-id>
        </item>
        <item xml:id="hint-code_series-titleInfo-compact">
            <help>
                <p> Enter here the title of the series you are cataloguing. If the title divides
                    into a main title and a subtitle, enter each part in its separate field. </p>
                <p> If you have chosen a transliteration scheme when you created the record, you
                    will have the option of entering a transliteration and a translation.</p>
                <p> If the title is in a language that is usually transliterated, enter the
                    transliterated title and subtitle in their respective fields. Use the
                    transliteration scheme you chose when selecting a record template. </p>
                <p> If you believe it is useful to supply a translation of the title, do so in the
                    relevant fields. If the language that the title information is translated into
                    is not English, you should choose another language. </p>
            </help>
            <value>series-titleInfo-compact</value>
            <local-name>titleInfo</local-name>
            <parent/>
            <tab-id>compact-b-monograph</tab-id>
        </item>
        <item xml:id="hint-code_edited-volume-series-title">
            <help>
                <p> Enter here the title of the series you are cataloguing. If the title divides
                    into a main title and a subtitle, enter each part in its separate field. </p>
                <p> If you have chosen a transliteration scheme when you created the record, you
                    will have the option of entering a transliteration and a translation.</p>
                <p> If the title is in a language that is usually transliterated, enter the
                    transliterated title and subtitle in their respective fields. Use the
                    transliteration scheme you chose when selecting a record template. </p>
                <p> If you believe it is useful to supply a translation of the title, do so in the
                    relevant fields. If the language that the title information is translated into
                    is not English, you should choose another language. </p>
            </help>
            <hint/>
            <value>edited-volume-series-title</value>
            <local-name>titleInfo</local-name>
            <parent/>
            <tab-id>compact-b-edited-volume</tab-id>
        </item>
        <item xml:id="hint-code_edited-volume-series-part">
            <help>
                <p> Use this field to indicate the volume of the series that the edited volume you
                    are cataloguing occurs in. </p>
            </help>
            <hint/>
            <value>edited-volume-series-part</value>
            <local-name>titleInfo</local-name>
            <parent/>
            <tab-id>compact-b-edited-volume</tab-id>
        </item>
        <item xml:id="hint-code_edited-volume-series">
            <help>
                <p>Record here, if applicable, information regarding the book series that the edited
                    volume is part of and the position of the edited volume with the series.</p>
                <p>Only these two items are registered here.</p>
            </help>
            <hint/>
            <value>edited-volume-series</value>
            <local-name>titleInfo</local-name>
            <parent/>
            <tab-id>titles</tab-id>
        </item>
        <item xml:id="hint-code_topic">
            <help>
                <p> Use Topic to indicate any primary subjects that do not fit into the Place, Time,
                    Works as Topics, or Persons and Institutions as Topics sub-fields. In general,
                    abstract nouns should be used. Add as many Topic fields as you need in order to
                    analyse your topic. The relation between the different fields is not specified,
                    but one may start with more abstract terms and move to more specific terms,
                    within the same Subject.</p>
                <p> Before adding a Topic, consider whether what you are cataloguing is not rather
                    another Subject. There are no hard-and-fast rules here, but it is best to
                    analyse as much as possible, i.e. if the term to be entered as a Topic is not a
                    specification of the Topic term already entered, one should probably add another
                    Subject instead of another Topic.</p>
                <p> More input options can be accessed by clicking the Subjects tab on Content
                    Description Forms.</p>
                <p> While it is highly recommended that subject values be parsed into sub-fields,
                    they are often listed as a string, divided by e.g. double dashes, as in Library
                    of Congress Subject Headings. If you have imported such Subjects, please analyse
                    them.</p>
            </help>
            <hint/>
            <value>topic</value>
            <local-name>topic</local-name>
            <parent/>
            <tab-id>compact-c</tab-id>
            <tab-id>compact-d</tab-id>
            <tab-id>subject</tab-id>
        </item>
        <item xml:id="hint-code_transliteration">
            <help>
                <p> Transliteration specifies the transliteration (transcription, romanisation)
                    scheme used within a certain field. When specifying the transliteration used,
                    also specify the language employed. Since only transliteration into Roman script
                    is used, there is no need to record the script used.</p>
                <p> There is at present no standard list of transliteration schemes available, but
                    use the American Library Association-Library of Congress transliteration, if
                    possible. These are postfixed "ALA-LC" in the drop-down list. For more
                    information on these transliteration schemes, see <a href="http://www.loc.gov/catdir/cpso/roman.html">http://www.loc.gov/catdir/cpso/roman.html</a> (ALA-LC Romanization Tables). </p>
                <p> If you wish to employ a transliteration scheme not in the list, please contact
                    &lt;tamboti-admins@asia-europe.uni-heidelberg.de&gt;. </p>
                <p> Apply transliteration as high as possible. For instance it is possible to apply
                    a transliteration to Origin Information as a whole. Do this if you are using
                    only one Transliteration value for all Place Terms, for Publisher and for
                    Edition. If you are using different Transliteration values inside e.g. Origin
                    Information, apply Transliteration to each field and leave Transliteration empty
                    under Origin Information. </p>
            </help>
            <hint/>
            <value>transliteration</value>
            <local-name>transliteration</local-name>
            <parent/>
            <tab-id>title</tab-id>
            <tab-id>name</tab-id>
            <tab-id>origin</tab-id>
            <tab-id>part</tab-id>
            <tab-id>related</tab-id>
            <tab-id>related-abbreviated</tab-id>
            <tab-id>related-xlink</tab-id>
            <tab-id>physical-description</tab-id>
            <tab-id>access-condition</tab-id>
            <tab-id>genre</tab-id>
            <tab-id>identifier</tab-id>
            <tab-id>language</tab-id>
            <tab-id>location</tab-id>
            <tab-id>mads</tab-id>
            <tab-id>note</tab-id>
            <tab-id>subject</tab-id>
            <tab-id>abstract</tab-id>
            <tab-id>target-audience</tab-id>
            <tab-id>record-info</tab-id>
            <tab-id>table-of-contents</tab-id>
            <tab-id>classification</tab-id>
        </item>
        <item xml:id="hint-code_transliteration-global-compact">
            <help>
                <p> Global Transliteration specifies the transliteration (transcription,
                    romanisation) scheme used.</p>
                <p> Note that the value shown here is the value chosen when the record template was
                    chosen. This value applies to the whole record, not just to the field above
                    which it is noted. If you change the value, the change will apply to the whole
                    record. </p>
                <p> The Global Transliteration can be overruled for a specific field by choosing a
                    Local Transliteration in Citation Forms.</p>
            </help>
            <hint/>
            <value>transliteration-global-compact</value>
            <local-name>transliteration</local-name>
            <parent/>
            <tab-id>compact-a</tab-id>
        </item>
        <item xml:id="hint-code_transliteration-local-compact">
            <help>
                <p> Transliteration specifies the transliteration (transcription, romanisation)
                    scheme used.</p>
                <p> The transliteration noted here is <em>not</em> the transliteration chosen when
                    the record was created. The transliteration noted here only applies to the
                    field(s) immediately below. Since a title or a name as a subject can be in any
                    language , the Global Transliteration can be overruled here by choosing a Local
                    Transliteration.</p>
            </help>
            <hint/>
            <value>transliteration-local-compact</value>
            <local-name>transliteration</local-name>
            <parent/>
            <tab-id>compact-d</tab-id>
        </item>
        <item xml:id="hint-code_transliterationOfResource">
            <help>
                <p> Choose one of the transliteration schemes listed below. The transliteration
                    schemes are the same as those used in the pre-entry options. </p>
                <p> If a record has not been made by use of Tamboti, if will not have this field,
                    but you can assign a transliteration scheme to it here. Doing so will make it
                    unnecessary to note which transliteration scheme is used for individual fields,
                    i.e. you can set this value once and for all here. Adding a transliteration
                    scheme here will not cause the Basic Input Forms to display transliteration
                    fields. If you wish to add transliterations for titles, names, etc., you have to
                    use the Citation Forms.</p>
                <p> If you have assigned the wrong transliteration scheme in the pre-entry dialogue,
                    you can change it here. The Basic Input Forms will still display fields for the
                    transliteration of titles, names, etc.</p>
            </help>
            <hint/>
            <value>transliterationOfResource</value>
            <local-name>transliterationOfResource</local-name>
            <parent>extension</parent>
            <tab-id>extension</tab-id>
        </item>
        <item xml:id="hint-code_identifier-type">
            <help>
                <p>Type identifies the type of identifier that is recorded.</p>
            </help>
            <value>identifier-type</value>
            <local-name>type</local-name>
            <parent/>
            <tab-id>identifier</tab-id>
        </item>
        <item xml:id="hint-code_titleInfo-type">
            <help>
                <p> Type identifies what type of Title Information is recorded. </p>
                <p> If the title is recorded as it appears on the title page, it does not have Type.
                    Use Type if the title is abbreviated, translated, alternative, or uniform (a
                    transliteration is here regarded as a form of translation). Choose "(none
                    selected)" to clear Type.</p>
                <p> When an abbreviated title is present, an Authority should be chosen. </p>
                <p> An alternative title may be a parallel title found in the authoritative title
                    information (in written works, typically the title page) or a title that does
                    not occur in the authoritative title information, e.g. a title found on a cover.
                    If the alternative title does not occur in the authoritative title information,
                    indicate in Display Label where the information comes from (e.g., "Cover
                    Title"). If the alternative title occurs in the authoritative title information,
                    it can e.g. be a translation or a transliteration of the main title information.
                    If a translated or a transliterated title occurs in the authoritative title
                    information of the work being catalogued, choose "Alternative" for Type and note
                    the language, transliteration and script of the title information, as
                    appropriate, if this is different from the language noted in Language of
                    Resource. If this is not the case and you have e.g. supplied the translation or
                    transliteration yourself, choose "Translated" for Type and note the language,
                    transliteration and script of the title information, as appropriate. </p>
                <p> A uniform title is a title that refers uniformly to a work that is known by
                    several titles, e.g. the works of Shakespeare or the Bible. When a uniform title
                    is present, an Authority for its selection should be chosen. </p>
            </help>
            <hint/>
            <value>titleInfo-type</value>
            <local-name>type</local-name>
            <parent/>
            <tab-id>title</tab-id>
            <tab-id>subject</tab-id>
        </item>
        <item xml:id="hint-code_accessCondition-type">
            <help>
                <p>Use the type attribute to indicate the type of restrictions (or lack thereof) on
                    use of the resource and/or restrictions on access to the material.</p>
                <p>There is no controlled list of types for Access Condition. Suggested values are:
                    "restriction on access" and "use and reproduction". Choose the value appropriate
                    or enter a type of your own. </p>
            </help>
            <hint/>
            <value>accessCondition-type</value>
            <local-name>type</local-name>
            <parent/>
            <tab-id>access-condition</tab-id>
        </item>
        <item xml:id="hint-code_genre-type">
            <help>
                <p>Distinguishes different aspects of genre, such as class, work type or style.</p>
            </help>
            <value>genre-type</value>
            <local-name>type</local-name>
            <parent>genre</parent>
            <tab-id>genre</tab-id>
        </item>
        <item xml:id="hint-code_genre-authority">
            <help>
                <p> The name of the authoritative list for a controlled value is recorded here. </p>
                <p> See http://www.loc.gov/standards/sourcelist/genre-form.html for a list of
                    authority files in this area. If you wish to employ an authority file that is
                    not included in the dropdown, please contact HRA. </p>
            </help>
            <value>genre-type</value>
            <local-name>type</local-name>
            <parent>genre</parent>
            <tab-id>genre</tab-id>
        </item>
        <item xml:id="hint-code_languageTerm-type">
            <help>
                <p>Hint</p>
            </help>
            <hint/>
            <value>languageTerm-type</value>
            <local-name>type</local-name>
            <parent>languageTerm</parent>
            <tab-id>language</tab-id>
        </item>
        <item xml:id="hint-code_location-type">
            <help>
                <p> Type Identifies the type of location recorded. Use Type to indicate different
                    kinds of locations if more specificity is needed, e.g. current, discovery,
                    former, creation. </p>
            </help>
            <value>location-type</value>
            <local-name>type</local-name>
            <parent>location</parent>
            <tab-id>location</tab-id>
        </item>
        <item xml:id="hint-code_name-type">
            <help>
                <p>The Type field can take the following values: family, conference, corporate, and
                    personal, .</p>
                <p> Use it to indicate whether the name is the name of a person or a family, the
                    name of a corporation or the name of a conference (or an event similar to a
                    conference).</p>
            </help>
            <value>name-type</value>
            <local-name>type</local-name>
            <parent>name</parent>
            <tab-id>name</tab-id>
            <tab-id>mads</tab-id>
            <tab-id>subject</tab-id>
        </item>
        <item xml:id="hint-code_note-type">
            <help>
                <p>Identifies what type of note is recorded.</p>
                <p>One can either select a value from the drop-down menu or enter a free-text
                    value.</p>
            </help>
            <hint/>
            <value>note-type</value>
            <local-name>type</local-name>
            <parent>note</parent>
            <tab-id>compact-c</tab-id>
            <tab-id>note</tab-id>
        </item>
        <item xml:id="hint-code_code-text">
            <help>
                <p> Type indicates whether the value is expressed in a coded or textual form. </p>
            </help>
            <hint/>
            <value>originInfo-type</value>
            <local-name>type</local-name>
            <parent>note</parent>
            <tab-id>origin</tab-id>
            <tab-id>language</tab-id>
            <tab-id>subject</tab-id>
        </item>
        <item xml:id="hint-code_url-compact">
            <help>
                <p> In URL, record the Uniform Resource Locator (URL) of the resource if it has been
                    accessed on the Internet.</p>
                <p> Note also the date of the last time you have accessed the resource.</p>
            </help>
            <hint/>
            <value>url-compact</value>
            <local-name>url</local-name>
            <parent/>
            <tab-id>compact-a</tab-id>
            <tab-id>compact-b-review</tab-id>
            <tab-id>compact-b-xlink</tab-id>
        </item>
        <item xml:id="hint-code_name-usage">
            <help>
                <p>Usage with the value "primary" can be used with repeated fields to indicate
                    special prominence of one that is useful for various special purposes such as
                    indexing.</p>
                <p>When applied to Name, "primary" indicates the name that would probably be used
                    when citing the resource. This is useful when there are several authors and for
                    citation purposes one is to be selected. The "primary" name would be used with
                    the resource title for the citation, and also would be the name that would be
                    associated with the uniform title when one is present.</p>
            </help>
            <hint/>
            <value>name-usage</value>
            <local-name>usage</local-name>
            <parent/>
            <tab-id>name</tab-id>
            <tab-id>mads</tab-id>
        </item>
        <item xml:id="hint-code_usage">
            <help>
                <p>Usage with the value "primary" can be used with repeated fields to indicate
                    special prominence of one that is useful for various special purposes such as
                    indexing.</p>
            </help>
            <hint/>
            <value>usage</value>
            <local-name>usage</local-name>
            <parent/>
            <tab-id>title</tab-id>
            <tab-id>language</tab-id>
            <tab-id>subject</tab-id>
            <tab-id>classification</tab-id>
            <tab-id>type</tab-id>
            <tab-id>genre</tab-id>
        </item>
        <item xml:id="hint-code_value-uri">
            <help>
                <p>A URI uniquely identifying the term or controlled value from a vocabulary, as
                    assigned by the body responsible for the maintenance of the vocabulary.</p>
                <p>URIs identifying terms may or may not be dereferenceable to human- or
                    machine-readable records for the term.</p>
            </help>
            <hint/>
            <value>value-uri</value>
            <local-name>valueURI</local-name>
            <parent/>
            <tab-id>compact-c</tab-id>
            <tab-id>name</tab-id>
            <tab-id>title</tab-id>
            <tab-id>origin</tab-id>
            <tab-id>physical-description</tab-id>
            <tab-id>language</tab-id>
            <tab-id>mads</tab-id>
            <tab-id>target-audience</tab-id>
            <tab-id>genre</tab-id>
            <tab-id>subject</tab-id>
            <tab-id>location</tab-id>
            <tab-id>classification</tab-id>
            <tab-id>record-info</tab-id>
        </item>
        <item xml:id="hint-code_xlink_href">
            <help>
                <p> XLink is used to reference an external resource, such as a second metadata
                    record, a Related Item or a Table of Contents. </p>
                <p> Records in Tamboti are identified by a "Universal Unique Identifier" (UUID),
                    prefixed with "uuid-". It has the form
                    "uuid-1a385342-5d6a-4abb-8704-4355f69dcec9." You can find this value in the
                    "Stable Link to This Record" in the detail view for each record.</p>
                <p>If you wish to refer to another Tamboti record by its ID in an XLink, you should
                    insert the UUID with a pound sign (#) in front of it. If you see a link of this
                    kind, only remove it if it points to the wrong record.</p>
            </help>
            <hint/>
            <value>xlink:href</value>
            <local-name>xlink:href</local-name>
            <parent/>
            <tab-id>compact-b-edited-volume</tab-id>
            <tab-id>compact-b-xlink</tab-id>
            <tab-id>name</tab-id>
            <tab-id>title</tab-id>
            <tab-id>part</tab-id>
            <tab-id>related</tab-id>
            <tab-id>related-abbreviated</tab-id>
            <tab-id>related-xlink</tab-id>
            <tab-id>physical-description</tab-id>
            <tab-id>location</tab-id>
            <tab-id>mads</tab-id>
            <tab-id>note</tab-id>
            <tab-id>subject</tab-id>
            <tab-id>table-of-contents</tab-id>
            <tab-id>abstract</tab-id>
        </item>
        <item xml:id="hint-code_accessCondition-xlink_href">
            <help>
                <p> The XLink field is used to reference an external resource, such as a second
                    metadata record, a Related Item or a Table Of Contents. </p>
                <p> An XLink may be supplied in lieu of or in addition to the content noted in
                    Access Condition. If, for example, you maintain rights information relating to
                    specific resources on a website, you may provide a URL for that website in lieu
                    of a textual rights statement. When doing so, you should provide enough textual
                    explanation in Access Condition, along with the URL, to make the purpose of the
                    URL clear to end users. </p>
            </help>
            <hint/>
            <value>accessCondition-xlink:href</value>
            <local-name>xlink:href</local-name>
            <parent/>
            <tab-id>access-condition</tab-id>
        </item>
        <item xml:id="hint-code_xlink_href-series">
            <help>
                <p> If the Book Series is catalogued elsewhere in Tamboti, enter its XLink here. </p>
                <p> You may delete the information entered below, if it is contained in the record
                    linked to by the XLink. </p>
            </help>
            <hint/>
            <value>xlink:href-series</value>
            <local-name>xlink:href</local-name>
            <parent/>
            <tab-id>compact-b-monograph</tab-id>
        </item>
        <item xml:id="hint-code_xlink_href-edited-volume">
            <help>
                <p> If the Edited Volume is catalogued elsewhere in Tamboti, enter its XLink here. </p>
                <p> You may delete the information entered below, if it is contained in the record
                    linked to by the XLink. </p>
            </help>
            <hint/>
            <value>xlink:href-edited-volume</value>
            <local-name>xlink:href</local-name>
            <parent/>
            <tab-id>compact-b-edited-volume</tab-id>
        </item>
        <item xml:id="hint-code_xlink_href-periodical">
            <help>
                <p> If the Periodical is catalogued elsewhere in Tamboti, enter its XLink here. </p>
                <p> You may delete the information entered below, if it is contained in the record
                    linked to by the XLink. </p>
            </help>
            <hint/>
            <value>xlink:href-periodical</value>
            <local-name>xlink:href</local-name>
            <parent/>
            <tab-id>titles</tab-id>
        </item>
        <item xml:id="hint-code_xlink_href-edited-volume">
            <help>
                <p> If the Edited Volume is catalogued elsewhere in Tamboti, enter its XLink here. </p>
                <p> You may delete the information entered below, if it is contained in the record
                    linked to by the XLink. </p>
            </help>
            <hint/>
            <value>xlink:href-edited-volume</value>
            <local-name>xlink:href</local-name>
            <parent/>
            <tab-id>titles</tab-id>
        </item>
        <item xml:id="hint-code_xml_lang">
            <help>
                <p> The language used within Title Information is specified here, if this language
                    is different from the language noted in Language of Resource. xml:lang is used
                    to specify the language used within a field, using specifications in RFC 3066.
                    RFC 3066 uses the two-character ISO 639-1 codes along with three-character ISO
                    639-2 codes for those languages not given in 639-1. </p>
                <p> The recommendation is not to use xml:lang, but to use Language. </p>
            </help>
            <hint/>
            <value>xml:lang</value>
            <local-name>xml:lang</local-name>
            <parent/>
            <tab-id>title</tab-id>
            <tab-id>name</tab-id>
            <tab-id>origin</tab-id>
            <tab-id>part</tab-id>
            <tab-id>related</tab-id>
            <tab-id>related-abbreviated</tab-id>
            <tab-id>related-xlink</tab-id>
            <tab-id>physical-description</tab-id>
            <tab-id>access-condition</tab-id>
            <tab-id>identifier</tab-id>
            <tab-id>genre</tab-id>
            <tab-id>language</tab-id>
            <tab-id>location</tab-id>
            <tab-id>mads</tab-id>
            <tab-id>note</tab-id>
            <tab-id>subject</tab-id>
            <tab-id>table-of-contents</tab-id>
            <tab-id>abstract</tab-id>
            <tab-id>target-audience</tab-id>
            <tab-id>classification</tab-id>
            <tab-id>record-info</tab-id>
        </item>
        <item xml:id="hint-code_reformattingQuality">
            <help>
                <p>Reformatting Quality indicates an overall assessment of the physical quality of
                    an electronic resource in relation to its intended use.</p>
                <p>The following values may be used: access, preservation and replacement.</p>
                <li>
                    <item>"access" indicates that the electronic resource is intended to support
                        current electronic access to the original item (i.e., reference use), but is
                        not sufficient to serve as a preservation copy.</item>
                    <item>"preservation" indicates that the electronic resource was created via
                        reformatting to help preserve the original item. The capture and storage
                        techniques ensure high-quality, long-term protection.</item>
                    <item>"replacement" indicates that the electronic resource is of high enough
                        quality to serve as a replacement if the original is lost, damaged, or
                        destroyed.</item>
                </li>
            </help>
            <hint/>
            <value>reformattingQuality</value>
            <local-name>reformattingQuality</local-name>
            <parent>physicalDescription</parent>
            <tab-id>physical-description</tab-id>
        </item>
    </items>
</code-table><!--return
for $item in $code-table/items/item
order by upper-case($item/local-name[1]), upper-case($item/parent) 
return $item-->