<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<div>
    <h4>Search syntax</h4>
    <p>
        Tamboti performs a search with the exact term you enter. A search for "Chin" does not retrieve all words beginning with "Chin"
        ("China", "Chinese" …), but only the word "Chin" itself.</p>
    <p>
        You can use <em>wildcards</em> to perform broader searches. "?" can be used as a wildcard for a single
        character and "*" for zero, one or more characters: "China" is thus found with "Ch?na" and
        "C*a", and "China" and "Chine" are found with "Chin?", just as "China", "Chine" and
        "Chinese" are all found with "Chin*". Note that "*" and "?" cannot occur in the
        beginning of a word.</p>
    <p>
        <em>Fuzzy searches</em> can be performed by putting "~" at the end of a word. To find "Chine", enter "China~". You can quantify the fuzziness, by appending
        a number between 0.0 and 1.0, "complete fuzziness" (finding everything) being 0.0 and
        complete identity being "1.0". 
        If you append a "~" with no number, the default value 0.5 is applied.</p>
    <p>
        <em>Phrases</em> can be searched for by putting them in quotation marks. Use "straight"
        double quotation marks only.</p>
    <p>
        Tamboti searches for the exact word order you enter. If you enter "Reform and Progress", you will
        only find records in which the three words occur in that exact sequence. Tamboti does not display records containing, for example, "Progress and Reform".</p>
    <p>
        Note that Chinese, Japanese and Korean characters are indexed as separate words, so a search
        for "日本" (without quotation marks) will find records with the two characters in the opposite
        order, that is, it will find records with "本日" as well. 
        However, if you enclose "日本" in quotation marks, you
        only retrieve records with the two characters in that specific sequence.</p>
    <p>
        You can use the <em>boolean operators</em> "AND" and "OR". If you search for "China AND
        Japan", you will find only records containing both terms. If you search for "China OR Japan",
        you will find records in which either one or both the two terms occur. A search with "AND"
        normally results in fewer records than a search with "OR". "NOT" can also be used. If you
        search for "China NOT Japan", you will only find records that have "China" but not "Japan".
        </p>
    <p>
        You can also make boolean searches using Advanced Search.</p>
    <p>
        You can use more advanced search functions by using parentheses: "(China OR Japan) NOT
        Korea" will find records in which the words "China" or "Japan" occur, but only those in
        which "Korea" does not occur.</p>
    <p>
        "AND", "OR" and "NOT" must be written with uppercase letters. Otherwise, searches are made using
        lower-case letters only, so writing "China" with initial lower-case "C" (as "china") has the exact same
        effect as using an initial upper-case "C". 
        This means that there is no way you can search for e.g. "Bush" without finding "bush" as well.
    </p>
</div>